{"id": "oodtest_0", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_0", "raw/question": "- x * A / F / D / B + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C * B * D * F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A / F / D / B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A / F / D / B = C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * A/F/D = C * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * A/F = C * B * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * A = C * B * D * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C * B * D * F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_1", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_1", "raw/question": "- D - B - A * x * C / F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / A * F / C -  B / A * F / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B - A * x * C / F = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * C / F = D + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x * C / F = -  D -  B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * C/F = -  D / A -  B / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * C = -  D / A * F -  B / A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / A * F / C -  B / A * F / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_2", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_2", "raw/question": "- B + F - A - x * D + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / D + F / D -  A / D + C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "F - A - x * D + C = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A - x * D + C = B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x * D + C = B - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * D = B - F + A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * D = -  B + F -  A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / D + F / D -  A / D + C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_3", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_3", "raw/question": "- C = F + B - x * D * A", "raw/answer": "x = C / D / A + F / D / A + B / D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + B - x * D * A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "B - x * D * A = - C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * D * A = - C - F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * D * A = C + F + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A = C / D + F / D + B / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C / D / A + F / D / A + B / D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_4", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_4", "raw/question": "- C = B - D * F * A * x", "raw/answer": "x = C / D / F / A + B / D / F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - D * F * A * x = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D * F * A * x = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * F * A * x = C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "F * A * x = C / D + B / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "A * x = C / D / F + B / D / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C / D / F / A + B / D / F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_5", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_5", "raw/question": "- B = F - x - C - A + D", "raw/answer": "x = B + F -  C -  A + D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - x - C - A + D = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x - C - A + D = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - A + D = - B - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + D = - B - F + C + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B - F + C + A - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B + F -  C -  A + D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_6", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_6", "raw/question": "- x + C - F + B - A + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C -  F + B -  A + D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - F + B - A + D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x + B - A + D = - C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x - A + D = - C + F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + D = - C + F - B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - C + F - B + A - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = C -  F + B -  A + D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_7", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_7", "raw/question": "F + D + C - A - B - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F + D + C -  A -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D + C - A - B - x = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "C - A - B - x = - F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - B - x = - F - D - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B - x = - F - D - C + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F - D - C + A + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F + D + C -  A -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_8", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_8", "raw/question": "- D + B + F + C - x * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / A + B / A + F / A + C / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "B + F + C - x * A = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F + C - x * A = D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "C - x * A = D - B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = D - B - F - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  D + B + F + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / A + B / A + F / A + C / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_9", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_9", "raw/question": "C - x * F * D * A + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / F / D / A + B / F / D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * F * D * A + B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * F * D * A = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F * D * A = C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * D * A = C / F + B / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A = C / F / D + B / F / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C / F / D / A + B / F / D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_10", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_10", "raw/question": "A - D * B / F * C / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (A / D * F / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D * B / F * C / x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * B / F * C / x = A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "B/F * C/x = A / D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "B * C/x = A / D * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "C/x = A / D * F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (A / D * F / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_11", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_11", "raw/question": "- D - B * x * C / A - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / B * A / C -  F / B * A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B * x * C / A - F = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- B * x * C / A = D + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x * C / A = -  D -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * C/A = -  D / B -  F / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x * C = -  D / B * A -  F / B * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / B * A / C -  F / B * A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_12", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_12", "raw/question": "C + B + F + D - A / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (C + B + F + D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B + F + D - A / x = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F + D - A / x = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D - A / x = - C - B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A / x = - C - B - F - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / x = C + B + F + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (C + B + F + D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_13", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_13", "raw/question": "C - A - x + B + D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C -  A + B + D + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - x + B + D + F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + B + D + F = - C + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x + D + F = - C + A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x + F = - C + A - B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - C + A - B - D - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = C -  A + B + D + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_14", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_14", "raw/question": "C - F * A / x * B - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (C / F / B -  D / F / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F * A / x * B - D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * A / x * B = - C + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * A / x * B = C -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "A/x * B = C / F -  D / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "A/x = C / F / B -  D / F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (C / F / B -  D / F / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_15", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_15", "raw/question": "C = D - B - A - x - F", "raw/answer": "x = - C + D -  B -  A -  F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - B - A - x - F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B - A - x - F = C - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A - x - F = C - D + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - F = C - D + B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x = C - D + B + A + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - C + D -  B -  A -  F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_16", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_16", "raw/question": "- A = B - x / F - D - C", "raw/answer": "x = A * F + B * F -  D * F -  C * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - x / F - D - C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / F - D - C = - A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F - C = - A - B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F = - A - B + D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F = A + B -  D -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = A * F + B * F -  D * F -  C * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_17", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_17", "raw/question": "- B = A - x - C - D - F", "raw/answer": "x = B + A -  C -  D -  F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - x - C - D - F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - C - D - F = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - F = - B - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - F = - B - A + C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B - A + C + D + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B + A -  C -  D -  F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_18", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_18", "raw/question": "B - A * x / F + D + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / A * F + D / A * F + C / A * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A * x / F + D + C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A * x / F + C = - B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A * x / F = - B - D - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x / F = B + D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/F = B / A + D / A + C / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = B / A * F + D / A * F + C / A * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_19", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_19", "raw/question": "- B = A - C - x * D / F", "raw/answer": "x = B * F / D + A * F / D -  C * F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - C - x * D / F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - x * D / F = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * D / F = - B - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * D / F = B + A -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * D = B * F + A * F -  C * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = B * F / D + A * F / D -  C * F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_20", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_20", "raw/question": "- F - A + D - B + C - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F -  A + D -  B + C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- A + D - B + C - x = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "D - B + C - x = F + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B + C - x = F + A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "C - x = F + A - D + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x = F + A - D + B - C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F -  A + D -  B + C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_21", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_21", "raw/question": "- D = F - B / C / A * x", "raw/answer": "x = D * A * C / B + F * A * C / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - B / C / A * x = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B / C / A * x = - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / C / A * x = D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "B/C * x = D * A + F * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "B * x = D * A * C + F * A * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = D * A * C / B + F * A * C / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_22", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_22", "raw/question": "- C + A - x / B - D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C * B + A * B -  D * B + F * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A - x / B - D + F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / B - D + F = C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + F = C - A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = C - A + D - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = -  C + A -  D + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C * B + A * B -  D * B + F * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_23", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_23", "raw/question": "D - A - C * F * B * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / C / F / B -  A / C / F / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A - C * F * B * x = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C * F * B * x = - D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * F * B * x = D -  A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "F * B * x = D / C -  A / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "B * x = D / C / F -  A / C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = D / C / F / B -  A / C / F / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_24", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_24", "raw/question": "A - C - x / F * D - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / D * F -  C / D * F -  B / D * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - x / F * D - B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * D - B = - A + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * D = - A + C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F * D = A -  C -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/F = A / D -  C / D -  B / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = A / D * F -  C / D * F -  B / D * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_25", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_25", "raw/question": "A - F / x / D / B * C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (A / C * B * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / D / B * C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x / D / B * C = A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "F/x/D/B = A / C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "F/x/D = A / C * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "F/x = A / C * B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (A / C * B * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_26", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_26", "raw/question": "A + C - B + F - D * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / D + C / D -  B / D + F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C - B + F - D * x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- B + F - D * x = - A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "F - D * x = - A - C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D * x = - A - C + B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * x = A + C -  B + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = A / D + C / D -  B / D + F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_27", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_27", "raw/question": "D = A - x / F / C - B", "raw/answer": "x = - D * C * F + A * C * F -  B * C * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - x / F / C - B = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / C - B = D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / C = D - A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F / C = - D + A -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x/F = - D * C + A * C -  B * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = - D * C * F + A * C * F -  B * C * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_28", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_28", "raw/question": "- x * B / A / D - C + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C * D * A / B + F * D * A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * B / A / D + F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * B / A / D = C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B / A / D = -  C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * B/A = -  C * D + F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x * B = -  C * D * A + F * D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C * D * A / B + F * D * A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_29", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_29", "raw/question": "F = C - B / x / D / A", "raw/answer": "x = B / (- F * A * D + C * A * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - B / x / D / A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- B / x / D / A = F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / x / D / A = - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "B/x/D = - F * A + C * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "B/x = - F * A * D + C * A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (- F * A * D + C * A * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_30", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_30", "raw/question": "B - A / x * C / F * D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (B * F / C / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A / x * C / F * D = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / x * C / F * D = B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "A/x * C * D = B * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "A/x * D = B * F / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "A/x = B * F / C / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (B * F / C / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_31", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_31", "raw/question": "- A + F - D / C * x + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A * C / D + F * C / D + B * C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "F - D / C * x + B = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D / C * x + B = A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D / C * x = A - F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / C * x = -  A + F + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "D * x = -  A * C + F * C + B * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A * C / D + F * C / D + B * C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_32", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_32", "raw/question": "- B / F * C * x / A - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D * F / B / C * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B / F * C * x / A = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / F * C * x / A = -  D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "B * C * x/A = -  D * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "C * x/A = -  D * F / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/A = -  D * F / B / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D * F / B / C * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_33", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_33", "raw/question": "- x / B + F + A - D - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F * B + A * B -  D * B -  C * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + A - D - C = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / B - D - C = - F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / B - C = - F - A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = - F - A + D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = F + A -  D -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = F * B + A * B -  D * B -  C * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_34", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_34", "raw/question": "D + F - x * C * B * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / C / B / A + F / C / B / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F - x * C * B * A = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * C * B * A = - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * C * B * A = D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * B * A = D / C + F / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * A = D / C / B + F / C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = D / C / B / A + F / C / B / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_35", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_35", "raw/question": "B - D * A * C / x / F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (B / D / A * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D * A * C / x / F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * A * C / x / F = B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "A * C/x/F = B / D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "C/x/F = B / D / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "C/x = B / D / A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (B / D / A * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_36", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_36", "raw/question": "- A - D - F * x * B / C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A / F * C / B -  D / F * C / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D - F * x * B / C = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * x * B / C = A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x * B / C = -  A -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * B/C = -  A / F -  D / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x * B = -  A / F * C -  D / F * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A / F * C / B -  D / F * C / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_37", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_37", "raw/question": "- A - F + D - C - x / B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A * B -  F * B + D * B -  C * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- F + D - C - x / B = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "D - C - x / B = A + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - x / B = A + F - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = A + F - D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = -  A -  F + D -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A * B -  F * B + D * B -  C * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_38", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_38", "raw/question": "C = D - B * x * A / F", "raw/answer": "x = - C / B * F / A + D / B * F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - B * x * A / F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B * x * A / F = C - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x * A / F = - C + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * A/F = - C / B + D / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - C / B * F + D / B * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / B * F / A + D / B * F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_39", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_39", "raw/question": "- x * B * C - A + D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A / B / C + D / B / C + F / B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x * B * C + D + F = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * B * C + F = A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * B * C = A - D - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B * C = -  A + D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * C = -  A / B + D / B + F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A / B / C + D / B / C + F / B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_40", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_40", "raw/question": "A = C - x * F / B * D", "raw/answer": "x = - A * B / F / D + C * B / F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - x * F / B * D = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * F / B * D = A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F / B * D = - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * F * D = - A * B + C * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * D = - A * B / F + C * B / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = - A * B / F / D + C * B / F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_41", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_41", "raw/question": "- F - D - x / A * B - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F / B * A -  D / B * A -  C / B * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D - x / A * B - C = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / A * B - C = F + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / A * B = F + D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A * B = -  F -  D -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/A = -  F / B -  D / B -  C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F / B * A -  D / B * A -  C / B * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_42", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_42", "raw/question": "F + D + C - x / A + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F * A + D * A + C * A + B * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D + C - x / A + B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "C - x / A + B = - F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / A + B = - F - D - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A = - F - D - C - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A = F + D + C + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = F * A + D * A + C * A + B * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_43", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_43", "raw/question": "A + B - x / F * C + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / C * F + B / C * F + D / C * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "B - x / F * C + D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * C + D = - A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * C = - A - B - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F * C = A + B + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/F = A / C + B / C + D / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = A / C * F + B / C * F + D / C * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_44", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_44", "raw/question": "- F = C - A - D - B - x", "raw/answer": "x = F + C -  A -  D -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - A - D - B - x = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - D - B - x = - F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D - B - x = - F - C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B - x = - F - C + A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F - C + A + D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F + C -  A -  D -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_45", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_45", "raw/question": "F - A * x * B / D + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / A * D / B + C / A * D / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * B / D + C = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * B / D = - F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x * B / D = F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * B/D = F / A + C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * B = F / A * D + C / A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = F / A * D / B + C / A * D / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_46", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_46", "raw/question": "F - A - B - x / C / D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F * D * C -  A * D * C -  B * D * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A - B - x / C / D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B - x / C / D = - F + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / C / D = - F + A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C / D = F -  A -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/C = F * D -  A * D -  B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = F * D * C -  A * D * C -  B * D * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_47", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_47", "raw/question": "B = A - x * C / F + D", "raw/answer": "x = - B * F / C + A * F / C + D * F / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - x * C / F + D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * C / F + D = B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * C / F = B - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * C / F = - B + A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * C = - B * F + A * F + D * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * F / C + A * F / C + D * F / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_48", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_48", "raw/question": "- F + B - A * x / C * D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F / A / D * C + B / A / D * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "B - A * x / C * D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A * x / C * D = F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x / C * D = -  F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/C * D = -  F / A + B / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/C = -  F / A / D + B / A / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F / A / D * C + B / A / D * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_49", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_49", "raw/question": "- C / D / x / B + A - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (A * B * D -  F * B * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C / D / x / B - F = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- C / D / x / B = - A + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / D / x / B = A -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "C/D/x = A * B -  F * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/ x = A * B * D -  F * B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (A * B * D -  F * B * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_50", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_50", "raw/question": "- C = A + D + B - x * F", "raw/answer": "x = C / F + A / F + D / F + B / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + D + B - x * F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D + B - x * F = - C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B - x * F = - C - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * F = - C - A - D - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F = C + A + D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = C / F + A / F + D / F + B / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_51", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_51", "raw/question": "A = B + D - x * F - C", "raw/answer": "x = - A / F + B / F + D / F -  C / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + D - x * F - C = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D - x * F - C = A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * F - C = A - B - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * F = A - B - D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F = - A + B + D -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = - A / F + B / F + D / F -  C / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_52", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_52", "raw/question": "D + F + A - x + B - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D + F + A + B -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F + A - x + B - C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "A - x + B - C = - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x + B - C = - D - F - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x - C = - D - F - A - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = - D - F - A - B + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = D + F + A + B -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_53", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_53", "raw/question": "A + D - F / x * C - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (A / C + D / C -  B / C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D - F / x * C - B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x * C - B = - A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F / x * C = - A - D + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x * C = A + D -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "F/x = A / C + D / C -  B / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (A / C + D / C -  B / C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_54", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_54", "raw/question": "- C = A - F / x / B + D", "raw/answer": "x = F / (C * B + A * B + D * B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - F / x / B + D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / B + D = - C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / B = - C - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x / B = C + A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "F/x = C * B + A * B + D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (C * B + A * B + D * B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_55", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_55", "raw/question": "B - x + F - A - D + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B + F -  A -  D + C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x + F - A - D + C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x - A - D + C = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - D + C = - B - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + C = - B - F + A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B - F + A + D - C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B + F -  A -  D + C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_56", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_56", "raw/question": "B + A - D / F / x + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (B * F + A * F + C * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A - D / F / x + C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D / F / x + C = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- D / F / x = - B - A - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / F / x = B + A + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "D/ x = B * F + A * F + C * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (B * F + A * F + C * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_57", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_57", "raw/question": "D - C * F / x - B - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (D / C -  B / C -  A / C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C * F / x - B - A = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C * F / x - A = - D + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C * F / x = - D + B + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * F / x = D -  B -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "F/x = D / C -  B / C -  A / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (D / C -  B / C -  A / C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_58", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_58", "raw/question": "- B + D + F + A - C * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / C + D / C + F / C + A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "D + F + A - C * x = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F + A - C * x = B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "A - C * x = B - D - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C * x = B - D - F - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x = -  B + D + F + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / C + D / C + F / C + A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_59", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_59", "raw/question": "- F - x / B * D + C - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F / D * B + C / D * B -  A / D * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B * D + C - A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / B * D - A = F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / B * D = F - C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B * D = -  F + C -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/B = -  F / D + C / D -  A / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F / D * B + C / D * B -  A / D * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_60", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_60", "raw/question": "- C / x * B + D + F - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (D / B + F / B -  A / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * B + F - A = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * B - A = - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * B = - D - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x * B = D + F -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "C/x = D / B + F / B -  A / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (D / B + F / B -  A / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_61", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_61", "raw/question": "D = A - B - x + F - C", "raw/answer": "x = - D + A -  B + F -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - B - x + F - C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B - x + F - C = D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x + F - C = D - A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x - C = D - A + B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = D - A + B - F + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - D + A -  B + F -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_62", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_62", "raw/question": "A - D - B / C / x / F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (A * F * C -  D * F * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D - B / C / x / F = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B / C / x / F = - A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / C / x / F = A -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "B/C/x = A * F -  D * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "B/ x = A * F * C -  D * F * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (A * F * C -  D * F * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_63", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_63", "raw/question": "- F - x - B - A - C - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F -  B -  A -  C -  D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x - B - A - C - D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x - A - C - D = F + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - C - D = F + B + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - D = F + B + A + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x = F + B + A + C + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F -  B -  A -  C -  D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_64", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_64", "raw/question": "- C + B + F - A - D / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (-  C + B + F -  A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "B + F - A - D / x = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F - A - D / x = C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A - D / x = C - B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D / x = C - B - F + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x = -  C + B + F -  A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (-  C + B + F -  A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_65", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_65", "raw/question": "- B / x / F * D - A + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (-  A / D * F + C / D * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B / x / F * D + C = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- B / x / F * D = A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / x / F * D = -  A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "B/x/F = -  A / D + C / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "B/x = -  A / D * F + C / D * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (-  A / D * F + C / D * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_66", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_66", "raw/question": "- x - D + F + A - B + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D + F + A -  B + C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + F + A - B + C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x + A - B + C = D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - B + C = D - F - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x + C = D - F - A + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x = D - F - A + B - C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D + F + A -  B + C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_67", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_67", "raw/question": "C - A - x * B / D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C * D / B -  A * D / B + F * D / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - x * B / D + F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x * B / D + F = - C + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * B / D = - C + A - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B / D = C -  A + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * B = C * D -  A * D + F * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = C * D / B -  A * D / B + F * D / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_68", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_68", "raw/question": "- C - B * F * x * D + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C / B / F / D + A / B / F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B * F * x * D + A = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B * F * x * D = C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * F * x * D = -  C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "F * x * D = -  C / B + A / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * D = -  C / B / F + A / B / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C / B / F / D + A / B / F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_69", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_69", "raw/question": "- x / D / A * C / F + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B * F / C * A * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / D / A * C / F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D / A * C / F = B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/D/A * C = B * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/D/A = B * F / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/D = B * F / C * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = B * F / C * A * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_70", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_70", "raw/question": "- A / C / B / x * F + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (D / F * B * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A / C / B / x * F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / C / B / x * F = D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "A/C/B/x = D / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "A/C/ x = D / F * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "A/ x = D / F * B * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (D / F * B * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_71", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_71", "raw/question": "D = B + C - A - F - x", "raw/answer": "x = - D + B + C -  A -  F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + C - A - F - x = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "C - A - F - x = D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - F - x = D - B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- F - x = D - B - C + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x = D - B - C + A + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - D + B + C -  A -  F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_72", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_72", "raw/question": "B - x * F - C + D + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / F -  C / F + D / F + A / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * F - C + D + A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * F + D + A = - B + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * F + A = - B + C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * F = - B + C - D - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F = B -  C + D + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = B / F -  C / F + D / F + A / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_73", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_73", "raw/question": "- x + C - A - D - B - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C -  A -  D -  B -  F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - A - D - B - F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - B - F = - C + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - B - F = - C + A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x - F = - C + A + D + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - C + A + D + B + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = C -  A -  D -  B -  F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_74", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_74", "raw/question": "C - F * x * A / B / D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / F * D * B / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F * x * A / B / D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x * A / B / D = C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * A/B/D = C / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * A/B = C / F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * A = C / F * D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C / F * D * B / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_75", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_75", "raw/question": "- F + B - x * A - D - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F / A + B / A -  D / A -  C / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "B - x * A - D - C = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * A - D - C = F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * A - C = F - B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = F - B + D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  F + B -  D -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F / A + B / A -  D / A -  C / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_76", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_76", "raw/question": "- x / D + A + F + C + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A * D + F * D + C * D + B * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + F + C + B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + C + B = - A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + B = - A - F - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / D = - A - F - C - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D = A + F + C + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = A * D + F * D + C * D + B * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_77", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_77", "raw/question": "F - C - x + B + A - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F -  C + B + A -  D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C - x + B + A - D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x + B + A - D = - F + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x + A - D = - F + C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - D = - F + C - B - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F + C - B - A + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F -  C + B + A -  D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_78", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_78", "raw/question": "- A - x / B + C + D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A * B + C * B + D * B + F * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + C + D + F = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + D + F = A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + F = A - C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = A - C - D - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = -  A + C + D + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A * B + C * B + D * B + F * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_79", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_79", "raw/question": "- C = A - x * F / D + B", "raw/answer": "x = C * D / F + A * D / F + B * D / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - x * F / D + B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * F / D + B = - C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * F / D = - C - A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F / D = C + A + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * F = C * D + A * D + B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = C * D / F + A * D / F + B * D / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_80", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_80", "raw/question": "- F = B - D * A * C / x", "raw/answer": "x = C / (F / D / A + B / D / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - D * A * C / x = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D * A * C / x = - F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * A * C / x = F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "A * C/x = F / D + B / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "C/x = F / D / A + B / D / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (F / D / A + B / D / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_81", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_81", "raw/question": "- C + A - B * F * x + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C / B / F + A / B / F + D / B / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A - B * F * x + D = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B * F * x + D = C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B * F * x = C - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * F * x = -  C + A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "F * x = -  C / B + A / B + D / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C / B / F + A / B / F + D / B / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_82", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_82", "raw/question": "A - F / x - B + D - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (A -  B + D -  C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x - B + D - C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F / x + D - C = - A + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x - C = - A + B - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x = - A + B - D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x = A -  B + D -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (A -  B + D -  C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_83", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_83", "raw/question": "- B = D + A - C + F - x", "raw/answer": "x = B + D + A -  C + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + A - C + F - x = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "A - C + F - x = - B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C + F - x = - B - D - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "F - x = - B - D - A + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B - D - A + C - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B + D + A -  C + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_84", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_84", "raw/question": "- x * B / F / A * C + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D * A * F / B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * B / F / A * C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B / F / A * C = D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x * B/F * C = D * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * B * C = D * A * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * C = D * A * F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = D * A * F / B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_85", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_85", "raw/question": "- x + A - D - F - B - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A -  D -  F -  B -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - F - B - C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - F - B - C = - A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x - B - C = - A + D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x - C = - A + D + F + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = - A + D + F + B + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = A -  D -  F -  B -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_86", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_86", "raw/question": "B - x * D * F / C * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / D * C / F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * D * F / C * A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * D * F / C * A = B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * F/C * A = B / D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x * F * A = B / D * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * A = B / D * C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = B / D * C / F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_87", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_87", "raw/question": "- B / A / D * x - C + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C * D * A / B + F * D * A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B / A / D * x + F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B / A / D * x = C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / A / D * x = -  C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "B/A * x = -  C * D + F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "B * x = -  C * D * A + F * D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C * D * A / B + F * D * A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_88", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_88", "raw/question": "F = A + D - x + C - B", "raw/answer": "x = - F + A + D + C -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + D - x + C - B = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D - x + C - B = F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x + C - B = F - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = F - A - D - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = F - A - D - C + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - F + A + D + C -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_89", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_89", "raw/question": "A - F - C / x * B / D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (A * D / B -  F * D / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F - C / x * B / D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * B / D = - A + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x * B / D = A -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/x * B = A * D -  F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "C/x = A * D / B -  F * D / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (A * D / B -  F * D / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_90", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_90", "raw/question": "- D - F - C + A - B * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / B -  F / B -  C / B + A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F - C + A - B * x = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- C + A - B * x = D + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A - B * x = D + F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B * x = D + F + C - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x = -  D -  F -  C + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / B -  F / B -  C / B + A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_91", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_91", "raw/question": "- F = B - D / x / A / C", "raw/answer": "x = D / (F * C * A + B * C * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - D / x / A / C = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D / x / A / C = - F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x / A / C = F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "D/x/A = F * C + B * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "D/x = F * C * A + B * C * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (F * C * A + B * C * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_92", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_92", "raw/question": "F = B - C / A / x / D", "raw/answer": "x = C / (- F * D * A + B * D * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - C / A / x / D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C / A / x / D = F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / A / x / D = - F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/A/x = - F * D + B * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C/ x = - F * D * A + B * D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (- F * D * A + B * D * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_93", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_93", "raw/question": "D = F + B + A - C - x", "raw/answer": "x = - D + F + B + A -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + B + A - C - x = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "B + A - C - x = D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A - C - x = D - F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - x = D - F - B - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = D - F - B - A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - D + F + B + A -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_94", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_94", "raw/question": "- C = B + A - D * F * x", "raw/answer": "x = C / D / F + B / D / F + A / D / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + A - D * F * x = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A - D * F * x = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D * F * x = - C - B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * F * x = C + B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "F * x = C / D + B / D + A / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = C / D / F + B / D / F + A / D / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_95", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_95", "raw/question": "- A - x + C - B - D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A + C -  B -  D + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + C - B - D + F = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - B - D + F = A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x - D + F = A - C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + F = A - C + B + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x = A - C + B + D - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A + C -  B -  D + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_96", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_96", "raw/question": "- C = B - A / F * x - D", "raw/answer": "x = C * F / A + B * F / A -  D * F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - A / F * x - D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A / F * x - D = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- A / F * x = - C - B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / F * x = C + B -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "A * x = C * F + B * F -  D * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C * F / A + B * F / A -  D * F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_97", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_97", "raw/question": "- D * x * A + B - C - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / D / A -  C / D / A -  F / D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D * x * A - C - F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- D * x * A - F = - B + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D * x * A = - B + C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * x * A = B -  C -  F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A = B / D -  C / D -  F / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = B / D / A -  C / D / A -  F / D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_98", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_98", "raw/question": "C = F - D * B * x * A", "raw/answer": "x = - C / D / B / A + F / D / B / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - D * B * x * A = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D * B * x * A = C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * B * x * A = - C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "B * x * A = - C / D + F / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - C / D / B + F / D / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / D / B / A + F / D / B / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_99", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_99", "raw/question": "B = C - F * A / x - D", "raw/answer": "x = A / (- B / F + C / F -  D / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - F * A / x - D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F * A / x - D = B - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * A / x = B - C + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * A / x = - B + C -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "A/x = - B / F + C / F -  D / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (- B / F + C / F -  D / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_100", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_100", "raw/question": "C + B - D * x + F + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / D + B / D + F / D + A / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B - D * x + F + A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D * x + F + A = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D * x + A = - C - B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D * x = - C - B - F - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * x = C + B + F + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = C / D + B / D + F / D + A / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_101", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_101", "raw/question": "- C - D - B / x - A + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (-  C -  D -  A + F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- D - B / x - A + F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B / x - A + F = C + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B / x + F = C + D + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B / x = C + D + A - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / x = -  C -  D -  A + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (-  C -  D -  A + F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_102", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_102", "raw/question": "D - F + B - C * x * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / C / A -  F / C / A + B / C / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F + B - C * x * A = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "B - C * x * A = - D + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C * x * A = - D + F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x * A = D -  F + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * A = D / C -  F / C + B / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = D / C / A -  F / C / A + B / C / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_103", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_103", "raw/question": "- C + A - F - D - x / B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C * B + A * B -  F * B -  D * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A - F - D - x / B = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F - D - x / B = C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D - x / B = C - A + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = C - A + F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = -  C + A -  F -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C * B + A * B -  F * B -  D * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_104", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_104", "raw/question": "A = B - F / x + C - D", "raw/answer": "x = F / (- A + B + C -  D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - F / x + C - D = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F / x + C - D = A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x - D = A - B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x = A - B - C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x = - A + B + C -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (- A + B + C -  D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_105", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_105", "raw/question": "F = C - A / x / D * B", "raw/answer": "x = A / (- F / B * D + C / B * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - A / x / D * B = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A / x / D * B = F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / x / D * B = - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "A/x/D = - F / B + C / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "A/x = - F / B * D + C / B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (- F / B * D + C / B * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_106", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_106", "raw/question": "F = B + C - x + A + D", "raw/answer": "x = - F + B + C + A + D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + C - x + A + D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "C - x + A + D = F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x + A + D = F - B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x + D = F - B - C - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x = F - B - C - A - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - F + B + C + A + D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_107", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_107", "raw/question": "- C = B - F / x + D - A", "raw/answer": "x = F / (C + B + D -  A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - F / x + D - A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F / x + D - A = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x - A = - C - B - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x = - C - B - D + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x = C + B + D -  A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (C + B + D -  A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_108", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_108", "raw/question": "- x * F / B + A + C - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A * B / F + C * B / F -  D * B / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * F / B + C - D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * F / B - D = - A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * F / B = - A - C + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F / B = A + C -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * F = A * B + C * B -  D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = A * B / F + C * B / F -  D * B / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_109", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_109", "raw/question": "D + F - A * x * C / B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / A * B / C + F / A * B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F - A * x * C / B = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * C / B = - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x * C / B = D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * C/B = D / A + F / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * C = D / A * B + F / A * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = D / A * B / C + F / A * B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_110", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_110", "raw/question": "- x - B + D - A + C + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B + D -  A + C + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x + D - A + C + F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x - A + C + F = B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + C + F = B - D + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x + F = B - D + A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x = B - D + A - C - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B + D -  A + C + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_111", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_111", "raw/question": "- F = B - x + A + C + D", "raw/answer": "x = F + B + A + C + D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - x + A + C + D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x + A + C + D = - F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x + C + D = - F - B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x + D = - F - B - A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F - B - A - C - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F + B + A + C + D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_112", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_112", "raw/question": "D + B + A + C - F / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (D + B + A + C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B + A + C - F / x = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A + C - F / x = - D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C - F / x = - D - B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x = - D - B - A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x = D + B + A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (D + B + A + C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_113", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_113", "raw/question": "- F + D - A * x * B - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F / A / B + D / A / B -  C / A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "D - A * x * B - C = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * B - C = F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * B = F - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x * B = -  F + D -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * B = -  F / A + D / A -  C / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F / A / B + D / A / B -  C / A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_114", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_114", "raw/question": "- B = F - A - D * x + C", "raw/answer": "x = B / D + F / D -  A / D + C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - A - D * x + C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A - D * x + C = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D * x + C = - B - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- D * x = - B - F + A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * x = B + F -  A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = B / D + F / D -  A / D + C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_115", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_115", "raw/question": "- B * x / F + A - C + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / B * F -  C / B * F + D / B * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B * x / F - C + D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B * x / F + D = - A + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B * x / F = - A + C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x / F = A -  C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/F = A / B -  C / B + D / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = A / B * F -  C / B * F + D / B * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_116", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_116", "raw/question": "- A - B * C * x + D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A / B / C + D / B / C + F / B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B * C * x + D + F = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B * C * x + F = A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B * C * x = A - D - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * C * x = -  A + D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "C * x = -  A / B + D / B + F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A / B / C + D / B / C + F / B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_117", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_117", "raw/question": "- D + C - A - F * x * B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / F / B + C / F / B -  A / F / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "C - A - F * x * B = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - F * x * B = D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- F * x * B = D - C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x * B = -  D + C -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * B = -  D / F + C / F -  A / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / F / B + C / F / B -  A / F / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_118", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_118", "raw/question": "B + A + D - C - F * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / F + A / F + D / F -  C / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A + D - C - F * x = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D - C - F * x = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - F * x = - B - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F * x = - B - A - D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x = B + A + D -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = B / F + A / F + D / F -  C / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_119", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_119", "raw/question": "- C + F - A * D / x - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (-  C / A + F / A -  B / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "F - A * D / x - B = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A * D / x - B = C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A * D / x = C - F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x = -  C + F -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "D/x = -  C / A + F / A -  B / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (-  C / A + F / A -  B / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_120", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_120", "raw/question": "- F * x * B / A + D + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / F * A / B + C / F * A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F * x * B / A + C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F * x * B / A = - D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x * B / A = D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * B/A = D / F + C / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x * B = D / F * A + C / F * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = D / F * A / B + C / F * A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_121", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_121", "raw/question": "- C * A * x / F / D - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / C / A * D * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C * A * x / F / D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * A * x / F / D = -  B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "A * x/F/D = -  B / C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/F/D = -  B / C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/F = -  B / C / A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / C / A * D * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_122", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_122", "raw/question": "- B + A - D * x - C + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / D + A / D -  C / D + F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "A - D * x - C + F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D * x - C + F = B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- D * x + F = B - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D * x = B - A + C - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * x = -  B + A -  C + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / D + A / D -  C / D + F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_123", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_123", "raw/question": "B - A * C / x / D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (B / A * D + F / A * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A * C / x / D + F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A * C / x / D = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * C / x / D = B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "C/x/D = B / A + F / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/x = B / A * D + F / A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (B / A * D + F / A * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_124", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_124", "raw/question": "- F = A - C / x * B * D", "raw/answer": "x = C / (F / B / D + A / B / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - C / x * B * D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * B * D = - F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x * B * D = F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "C/x * D = F / B + A / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "C/x = F / B / D + A / B / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (F / B / D + A / B / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_125", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_125", "raw/question": "- D = F - C / x / A / B", "raw/answer": "x = C / (D * B * A + F * B * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - C / x / A / B = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C / x / A / B = - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x / A / B = D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "C/x/A = D * B + F * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C/x = D * B * A + F * B * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (D * B * A + F * B * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_126", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_126", "raw/question": "C - F * D * x * A / B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / F / D * B / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F * D * x * A / B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * D * x * A / B = C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "D * x * A/B = C / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A/B = C / F / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * A = C / F / D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C / F / D * B / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_127", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_127", "raw/question": "B = C - x / A + F - D", "raw/answer": "x = - B * A + C * A + F * A -  D * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - x / A + F - D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / A + F - D = B - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - D = B - C - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / A = B - C - F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A = - B + C + F -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * A + C * A + F * A -  D * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_128", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_128", "raw/question": "B + A + F + D - C * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / C + A / C + F / C + D / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A + F + D - C * x = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "F + D - C * x = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D - C * x = - B - A - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C * x = - B - A - F - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x = B + A + F + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / C + A / C + F / C + D / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_129", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_129", "raw/question": "C = A - D - x / F + B", "raw/answer": "x = - C * F + A * F -  D * F + B * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - D - x / F + B = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D - x / F + B = C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F + B = C - A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / F = C - A + D - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F = - C + A -  D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = - C * F + A * F -  D * F + B * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_130", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_130", "raw/question": "- C / F * x - B - D - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B * F / C -  D * F / C -  A * F / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C / F * x - D - A = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- C / F * x - A = B + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C / F * x = B + D + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / F * x = -  B -  D -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "C * x = -  B * F -  D * F -  A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B * F / C -  D * F / C -  A * F / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_131", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_131", "raw/question": "A - x / D * C - F + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / C * D -  F / C * D + B / C * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / D * C - F + B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / D * C + B = - A + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / D * C = - A + F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D * C = A -  F + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/D = A / C -  F / C + B / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = A / C * D -  F / C * D + B / C * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_132", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_132", "raw/question": "- A - x / F / B * C - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A / C * B * F -  D / C * B * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / B * C - D = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / B * C = A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F / B * C = -  A -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/F/B = -  A / C -  D / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/F = -  A / C * B -  D / C * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A / C * B * F -  D / C * B * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_133", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_133", "raw/question": "- x * A - D + C - B - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / A + C / A -  B / A -  F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * A + C - B - F = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A - B - F = D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x * A - F = D - C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = D - C + B + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  D + C -  B -  F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / A + C / A -  B / A -  F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_134", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_134", "raw/question": "- F / A * D * x + B - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B * A / F / D -  C * A / F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F / A * D * x - C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F / A * D * x = - B + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / A * D * x = B -  C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "F * D * x = B * A -  C * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "D * x = B * A / F -  C * A / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = B * A / F / D -  C * A / F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_135", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_135", "raw/question": "- B - F * A * C * x - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / F / A / C -  D / F / A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F * A * C * x - D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * A * C * x = B + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * A * C * x = -  B -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "A * C * x = -  B / F -  D / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "C * x = -  B / F / A -  D / F / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / F / A / C -  D / F / A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_136", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_136", "raw/question": "- B / A * C * D * x + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F * A / B / C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B / A * C * D * x = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / A * C * D * x = F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "B * C * D * x = F * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "C * D * x = F * A / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "D * x = F * A / B / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = F * A / B / C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_137", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_137", "raw/question": "- F / x + A - D + C + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (A -  D + C + B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x - D + C + B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x + C + B = - A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x + B = - A + D - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F / x = - A + D - C - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x = A -  D + C + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (A -  D + C + B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_138", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_138", "raw/question": "- F - D / C / B * A * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F * B * C / D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D / C / B * A * x = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / C / B * A * x = -  F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "D/C * A * x = -  F * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "D * A * x = -  F * B * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "A * x = -  F * B * C / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F * B * C / D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_139", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_139", "raw/question": "- D / x * B + C + F - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (C / B + F / B -  A / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- D / x * B + F - A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D / x * B - A = - C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D / x * B = - C - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x * B = C + F -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "D/x = C / B + F / B -  A / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (C / B + F / B -  A / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_140", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_140", "raw/question": "B = F - D / x / C * A", "raw/answer": "x = D / (- B / A * C + F / A * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - D / x / C * A = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D / x / C * A = B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x / C * A = - B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "D/x/C = - B / A + F / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "D/x = - B / A * C + F / A * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (- B / A * C + F / A * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_141", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_141", "raw/question": "A - B + C - x - F - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A -  B + C -  F -  D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B + C - x - F - D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "C - x - F - D = - A + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - F - D = - A + B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x - D = - A + B - C + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - A + B - C + F + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = A -  B + C -  F -  D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_142", "variable_num": 6, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_142", "raw/question": "C - x - A - F - D - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C -  A -  F -  D -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - A - F - D - B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - F - D - B = - C + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - B = - C + A + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = - C + A + F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = - C + A + F + D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = C -  A -  F -  D -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_143", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_143", "raw/question": "- G + B + D / F / x + C + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (G * F - B * F - C * F - A * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "B + D / F / x + C + A = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D / F / x + C + A = G - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "D / F / x + A = G - B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D / F / x = G - B - C - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "D/ x = G * F - B * F - C * F - A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (G * F - B * F - C * F - A * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_144", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_144", "raw/question": "- D = F * C + A - G - x * B", "raw/answer": "x = D / B + F * C / B + A / B -  G / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F * C + A - G - x * B = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F * C to the right side", "equation": "A - G - x * B = - D - F * C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G - x * B = - D - F * C - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x * B = - D - F * C - A + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B = D + F * C + A -  G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = D / B + F * C / B + A / B -  G / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_145", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_145", "raw/question": "F = C - G + D * B / x * A", "raw/answer": "x = B / (F / D / A - C / D / A + G / D / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - G + D * B / x * A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G + D * B / x * A = F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "D * B / x * A = F - C + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "B/x * A = F / D - C / D + G / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "B/x = F / D / A - C / D / A + G / D / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (F / D / A - C / D / A + G / D / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_146", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_146", "raw/question": "- x / F * G / B + D + A - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D * B / G * F + A * B / G * F -  C * B / G * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * G / B + A - C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * G / B - C = - D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * G / B = - D - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F * G / B = D + A -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/F * G = D * B + A * B -  C * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/F = D * B / G + A * B / G -  C * B / G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = D * B / G * F + A * B / G * F -  C * B / G * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_147", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_147", "raw/question": "- D / A = G + C + B + F - x", "raw/answer": "x = D / A + G + C + B + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + C + B + F - x = - D / A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C + B + F - x = - D / A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B + F - x = - D / A - G - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F - x = - D / A - G - C - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - D / A - G - C - B - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = D / A + G + C + B + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_148", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_148", "raw/question": "B = D + F / A + C - G / x", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- B + D + F / A + C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + F / A + C - G / x = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F / A + C - G / x = B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F / A to the right side", "equation": "C - G / x = B - D - F / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G / x = B - D - F / A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / x = - B + D + F / A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- B + D + F / A + C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_149", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_149", "raw/question": "B = F + D - C + A - G * x", "raw/answer": "x = - B / G + F / G + D / G -  C / G + A / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + D - C + A - G * x = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D - C + A - G * x = B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C + A - G * x = B - F - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A - G * x = B - F - D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x = B - F - D + C - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x = - B + F + D -  C + A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / G + F / G + D / G -  C / G + A / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_150", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_150", "raw/question": "- C = x * G + F + B + D + A", "raw/answer": "x = - C / G - F / G - B / G - D / G - A / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x * G + F + B + D + A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x * G + B + D + A = - C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x * G + D + A = - C - F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x * G + A = - C - F - B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x * G = - C - F - B - D - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / G - F / G - B / G - D / G - A / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_151", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_151", "raw/question": "- F - G + C * B - D - x * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F / A -  G / A + C * B / A -  D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G + C * B - D - x * A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "C * B - D - x * A = F + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C * B to the right side", "equation": "- D - x * A = F + G - C * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = F + G - C * B + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  F -  G + C * B -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F / A -  G / A + C * B / A -  D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_152", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_152", "raw/question": "- G - A - C / F - B * D / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (-  G / B -  A / B -  C / F / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- A - C / F - B * D / x = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C / F - B * D / x = G + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C / F to the right side", "equation": "- B * D / x = G + A + C / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * D / x = -  G -  A -  C / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "D/x = -  G / B -  A / B -  C / F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (-  G / B -  A / B -  C / F / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_153", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_153", "raw/question": "- G * x + F + B + C + D + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / G + B / G + C / G + D / G + A / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + B + C + D + A = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + C + D + A = - F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + D + A = - F - B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + A = - F - B - C - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x = - F - B - C - D - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x = F + B + C + D + A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = F / G + B / G + C / G + D / G + A / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_154", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_154", "raw/question": "F = G + B - x - A - D + C", "raw/answer": "x = - F + G + B -  A -  D + C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + B - x - A - D + C = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "B - x - A - D + C = F - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x - A - D + C = F - G - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - D + C = F - G - B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + C = F - G - B + A + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x = F - G - B + A + D - C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - F + G + B -  A -  D + C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_155", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_155", "raw/question": "- A = D - G - C + B + F / x", "raw/answer": "x = F / (- A - D + G + C - B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - G - C + B + F / x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- G - C + B + F / x = - A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- C + B + F / x = - A - D + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "B + F / x = - A - D + G + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F / x = - A - D + G + C - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (- A - D + G + C - B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_156", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_156", "raw/question": "A = B * F * x + D - C - G", "raw/answer": "x = A / B / F - D / B / F + C / B / F + G / B / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B * F * x + D - C - G = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B * F * x - C - G = A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "B * F * x - G = A - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "B * F * x = A - D + C + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "F * x = A / B - D / B + C / B + G / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = A / B / F - D / B / F + C / B / F + G / B / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_157", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_157", "raw/question": "G = F + D * C - x + A - B", "raw/answer": "x = - G + F + D * C + A -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + D * C - x + A - B = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D * C - x + A - B = G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D * C to the right side", "equation": "- x + A - B = G - F - D * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = G - F - D * C - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = G - F - D * C - A + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - G + F + D * C + A -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_158", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_158", "raw/question": "C / F / x + G + D + A + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (- G * F - D * F - A * F - B * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C / F / x + D + A + B = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "C / F / x + A + B = - G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C / F / x + B = - G - D - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "C / F / x = - G - D - A - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "C/ x = - G * F - D * F - A * F - B * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (- G * F - D * F - A * F - B * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_159", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_159", "raw/question": "G + D + C - F - A - x - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G + D + C -  F -  A -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "D + C - F - A - x - B = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "C - F - A - x - B = - G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F - A - x - B = - G - D - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- A - x - B = - G - D - C + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = - G - D - C + F + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = - G - D - C + F + A + B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = G + D + C -  F -  A -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_160", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_160", "raw/question": "F = B - A + D + C / x / G", "raw/answer": "x = C / (F * G - B * G + A * G - D * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - A + D + C / x / G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A + D + C / x / G = F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "D + C / x / G = F - B + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "C / x / G = F - B + A - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "C/x = F * G - B * G + A * G - D * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (F * G - B * G + A * G - D * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_161", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_161", "raw/question": "- C = B - x + A / F - D - G", "raw/answer": "x = C + B + A / F -  D -  G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - x + A / F - D - G = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x + A / F - D - G = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A / F to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - G = - C - B - A / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - G = - C - B - A / F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - C - B - A / F + D + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = C + B + A / F -  D -  G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_162", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_162", "raw/question": "C = B - A * x * D / F - G", "raw/answer": "x = - C / A * F / D + B / A * F / D -  G / A * F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - A * x * D / F - G = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * D / F - G = C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * D / F = C - B + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x * D / F = - C + B -  G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * D/F = - C / A + B / A -  G / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * D = - C / A * F + B / A * F -  G / A * F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / A * F / D + B / A * F / D -  G / A * F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_163", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_163", "raw/question": "F = C - A - x - G + D / B", "raw/answer": "x = - F + C -  A -  G + D / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - A - x - G + D / B = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - x - G + D / B = F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - G + D / B = F - C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x + D / B = F - C + A + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D / B to the right side", "equation": "- x = F - C + A + G - D / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - F + C -  A -  G + D / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_164", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_164", "raw/question": "- x * D * G * B + A / C - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / C / D / G / B -  F / D / G / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A / C to the right side", "equation": "- x * D * G * B - F = - A / C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x * D * G * B = - A / C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * D * G * B = A / C -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * G * B = A / C / D -  F / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * B = A / C / D / G -  F / D / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = A / C / D / G / B -  F / D / G / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_165", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_165", "raw/question": "- C = B * F + A - x * G / D", "raw/answer": "x = C * D / G + B * F * D / G + A * D / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B * F + A - x * G / D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B * F to the right side", "equation": "A - x * G / D = - C - B * F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * G / D = - C - B * F - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G / D = C + B * F + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * G = C * D + B * F * D + A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = C * D / G + B * F * D / G + A * D / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_166", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_166", "raw/question": "- x * C + G + F - A - B + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / C + F / C -  A / C -  B / C + D / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x * C + F - A - B + D = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * C - A - B + D = - G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x * C - B + D = - G - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x * C + D = - G - F + A + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * C = - G - F + A + B - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * C = G + F -  A -  B + D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = G / C + F / C -  A / C -  B / C + D / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_167", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_167", "raw/question": "B - A - C - x - F * D + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B -  A -  C -  F * D + G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A - C - x - F * D + G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C - x - F * D + G = - B + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - F * D + G = - B + A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F * D to the right side", "equation": "- x + G = - B + A + C + F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B + A + C + F * D - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B -  A -  C -  F * D + G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_168", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_168", "raw/question": "G = x / C / A * B * D - F", "raw/answer": "x = G / B / D * A * C + F / B / D * A * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x / C / A * B * D - F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x / C / A * B * D = G + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/C/A * D = G / B + F / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/C/A = G / B / D + F / B / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/C = G / B / D * A + F / B / D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = G / B / D * A * C + F / B / D * A * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_169", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_169", "raw/question": "- F = G / A * x * C / B * D", "raw/answer": "x = - F * A / G * B / C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G / A * x * C / B * D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "G * x * C/B * D = - F * A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * C/B * D = - F * A / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * C * D = - F * A / G * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * D = - F * A / G * B / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * A / G * B / C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_170", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_170", "raw/question": "- C = D / G - B - A - x - F", "raw/answer": "x = C + D / G -  B -  A -  F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D / G - B - A - x - F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D / G to the right side", "equation": "- B - A - x - F = - C - D / G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A - x - F = - C - D / G + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - F = - C - D / G + B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - C - D / G + B + A + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = C + D / G -  B -  A -  F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_171", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_171", "raw/question": "- A = B + D + F / x * G * C", "raw/answer": "x = F / (- A / G / C - B / G / C - D / G / C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + D + F / x * G * C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D + F / x * G * C = - A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F / x * G * C = - A - B - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "F/x * C = - A / G - B / G - D / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "F/x = - A / G / C - B / G / C - D / G / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (- A / G / C - B / G / C - D / G / C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_172", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_172", "raw/question": "B = F - A + D / x * C / G", "raw/answer": "x = D / (B * G / C - F * G / C + A * G / C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - A + D / x * C / G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A + D / x * C / G = B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "D / x * C / G = B - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "D/x * C = B * G - F * G + A * G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "D/x = B * G / C - F * G / C + A * G / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (B * G / C - F * G / C + A * G / C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_173", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_173", "raw/question": "F = B - A - C - x + G - D", "raw/answer": "x = - F + B -  A -  C + G -  D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - A - C - x + G - D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A - C - x + G - D = F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C - x + G - D = F - B + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x + G - D = F - B + A + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - D = F - B + A + C - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x = F - B + A + C - G + D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - F + B -  A -  C + G -  D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_174", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_174", "raw/question": "D * F + B + A + C - x * G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D * F / G + B / G + A / G + C / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D * F to the right side", "equation": "B + A + C - x * G = - D * F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A + C - x * G = - D * F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C - x * G = - D * F - B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * G = - D * F - B - A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G = D * F + B + A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = D * F / G + B / G + A / G + C / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_175", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_175", "raw/question": "- D = G * x + C + A + B + F", "raw/answer": "x = - D / G - C / G - A / G - B / G - F / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G * x + C + A + B + F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G * x + A + B + F = - D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G * x + B + F = - D - C - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G * x + F = - D - C - A - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "G * x = - D - C - A - B - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / G - C / G - A / G - B / G - F / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_176", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_176", "raw/question": "- B = D * G - C - x * A + F", "raw/answer": "x = B / A + D * G / A -  C / A + F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D * G - C - x * A + F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D * G to the right side", "equation": "- C - x * A + F = - B - D * G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A + F = - B - D * G + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = - B - D * G + C - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = B + D * G -  C + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = B / A + D * G / A -  C / A + F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_177", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_177", "raw/question": "D - A - B + F + C * x - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - D / C + A / C + B / C - F / C + G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A - B + F + C * x - G = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B + F + C * x - G = - D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "F + C * x - G = - D + A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "C * x - G = - D + A + B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "C * x = - D + A + B - F + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / C + A / C + B / C - F / C + G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_178", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_178", "raw/question": "- F = C + D + G * A * x - B", "raw/answer": "x = - F / G / A - C / G / A - D / G / A + B / G / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C + D + G * A * x - B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "D + G * A * x - B = - F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "G * A * x - B = - F - C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G * A * x = - F - C - D + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "A * x = - F / G - C / G - D / G + B / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F / G / A - C / G / A - D / G / A + B / G / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_179", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_179", "raw/question": "- C + G * A * F * x + B - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / G / A / F - B / G / A / F + D / G / A / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "G * A * F * x + B - D = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G * A * F * x - D = C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "G * A * F * x = C - B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "A * F * x = C / G - B / G + D / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "F * x = C / G / A - B / G / A + D / G / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = C / G / A / F - B / G / A / F + D / G / A / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_180", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_180", "raw/question": "C - A - x / B - F + G = D", "raw/answer": "x = - D * B + C * B -  A * B -  F * B + G * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A - x / B - F + G = D - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / B - F + G = D - C + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + G = D - C + A + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = D - C + A + F - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = - D + C -  A -  F + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = - D * B + C * B -  A * B -  F * B + G * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_181", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_181", "raw/question": "- D = F - B / G * A / C / x", "raw/answer": "x = A / (D * G / B * C + F * G / B * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - B / G * A / C / x = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B / G * A / C / x = - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / G * A / C / x = D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "B * A/C/x = D * G + F * G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "A/C/x = D * G / B + F * G / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "A/ x = D * G / B * C + F * G / B * C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (D * G / B * C + F * G / B * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_182", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_182", "raw/question": "- B = F - C + x * G / A * D", "raw/answer": "x = - B * A / G / D - F * A / G / D + C * A / G / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - C + x * G / A * D = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C + x * G / A * D = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x * G / A * D = - B - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x * G * D = - B * A - F * A + C * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * D = - B * A / G - F * A / G + C * A / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * A / G / D - F * A / G / D + C * A / G / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_183", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_183", "raw/question": "B = A - x - G - D - C * F", "raw/answer": "x = - B + A -  G -  D -  C * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - x - G - D - C * F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - G - D - C * F = B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - C * F = B - A + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - C * F = B - A + G + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C * F to the right side", "equation": "- x = B - A + G + D + C * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - B + A -  G -  D -  C * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_184", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_184", "raw/question": "G = B / x / A / D + C + F", "raw/answer": "x = B / (G * D * A - C * D * A - F * D * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B / x / A / D + C + F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B / x / A / D + F = G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "B / x / A / D = G - C - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "B/x/A = G * D - C * D - F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "B/x = G * D * A - C * D * A - F * D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (G * D * A - C * D * A - F * D * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_185", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_185", "raw/question": "- F * C * x * A + G + D - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / F / C / A + D / F / C / A -  B / F / C / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- F * C * x * A + D - B = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F * C * x * A - B = - G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F * C * x * A = - G - D + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * C * x * A = G + D -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "C * x * A = G / F + D / F -  B / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * A = G / F / C + D / F / C -  B / F / C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = G / F / C / A + D / F / C / A -  B / F / C / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_186", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_186", "raw/question": "- G - x - A + B + F + C * D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G -  A + B + F + C * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x - A + B + F + C * D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + B + F + C * D = G + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x + F + C * D = G + A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x + C * D = G + A - B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C * D to the right side", "equation": "- x = G + A - B - F - C * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G -  A + B + F + C * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_187", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_187", "raw/question": "- G - F - B - x / D * C - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G / C * D -  F / C * D -  B / C * D -  A / C * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- F - B - x / D * C - A = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- B - x / D * C - A = G + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / D * C - A = G + F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / D * C = G + F + B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D * C = -  G -  F -  B -  A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/D = -  G / C -  F / C -  B / C -  A / C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G / C * D -  F / C * D -  B / C * D -  A / C * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_188", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_188", "raw/question": "B = C / A / F * x * D * G", "raw/answer": "x = B * F * A / C / D / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C / A / F * x * D * G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "C/A * x * D * G = B * F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C * x * D * G = B * F * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * D * G = B * F * A / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * G = B * F * A / C / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = B * F * A / C / D / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_189", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_189", "raw/question": "G = B / C * A * D * x * F", "raw/answer": "x = G * C / B / A / D / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B / C * A * D * x * F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "B * A * D * x * F = G * C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "A * D * x * F = G * C / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "D * x * F = G * C / B / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * F = G * C / B / A / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = G * C / B / A / D / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_190", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_190", "raw/question": "- F / G / A / x + D - C + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (D * A * G -  C * A * G + B * A * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / G / A / x - C + B = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F / G / A / x + B = - D + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F / G / A / x = - D + C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / G / A / x = D -  C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "F/G/ x = D * A -  C * A + B * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "F/ x = D * A * G -  C * A * G + B * A * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (D * A * G -  C * A * G + B * A * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_191", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_191", "raw/question": "A - F / x / G - C + D + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (A * G -  C * G + D * G + B * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / G - C + D + B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / G + D + B = - A + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / G + B = - A + C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / G = - A + C - D - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x / G = A -  C + D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "F/x = A * G -  C * G + D * G + B * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (A * G -  C * G + D * G + B * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_192", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_192", "raw/question": "A = x * D / C / G / B + F", "raw/answer": "x = A * B * G * C / D - F * B * G * C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x * D / C / G / B + F = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x * D / C / G / B = A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * D/C/G = A * B - F * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x * D/C = A * B * G - F * B * G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x * D = A * B * G * C - F * B * G * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = A * B * G * C / D - F * B * G * C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_193", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_193", "raw/question": "- A = F - G * x * B * D - C", "raw/answer": "x = A / G / B / D + F / G / B / D -  C / G / B / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - G * x * B * D - C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x * B * D - C = - A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x * B * D = - A - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x * B * D = A + F -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * B * D = A / G + F / G -  C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * D = A / G / B + F / G / B -  C / G / B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = A / G / B / D + F / G / B / D -  C / G / B / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_194", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_194", "raw/question": "- F + A + G * C * x - B + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / G / C - A / G / C + B / G / C - D / G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "A + G * C * x - B + D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G * C * x - B + D = F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G * C * x + D = F - A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "G * C * x = F - A + B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "C * x = F / G - A / G + B / G - D / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = F / G / C - A / G / C + B / G / C - D / G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_195", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_195", "raw/question": "A * x * C + G + B + F + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - G / A / C - B / A / C - F / A / C - D / A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "A * x * C + B + F + D = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A * x * C + F + D = - G - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "A * x * C + D = - G - B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "A * x * C = - G - B - F - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * C = - G / A - B / A - F / A - D / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = - G / A / C - B / A / C - F / A / C - D / A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_196", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_196", "raw/question": "- F = A / D + C - x - B + G", "raw/answer": "x = F + A / D + C -  B + G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A / D + C - x - B + G = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A / D to the right side", "equation": "C - x - B + G = - F - A / D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - B + G = - F - A / D - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x + G = - F - A / D - C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F - A / D - C + B - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F + A / D + C -  B + G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_197", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_197", "raw/question": "B = G / C - x / F + A + D", "raw/answer": "x = - B * F + G / C * F + A * F + D * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G / C - x / F + A + D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G / C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F + A + D = B - G / C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / F + D = B - G / C - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F = B - G / C - A - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F = - B + G / C + A + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * F + G / C * F + A * F + D * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_198", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_198", "raw/question": "- G + F - A / B * C * x + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G * B / A / C + F * B / A / C + D * B / A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "F - A / B * C * x + D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A / B * C * x + D = G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A / B * C * x = G - F - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / B * C * x = -  G + F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "A * C * x = -  G * B + F * B + D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "C * x = -  G * B / A + F * B / A + D * B / A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G * B / A / C + F * B / A / C + D * B / A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_199", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_199", "raw/question": "C = B + x / F * G * D * A", "raw/answer": "x = C / G / D / A * F - B / G / D / A * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + x / F * G * D * A = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x / F * G * D * A = C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/F * D * A = C / G - B / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/F * A = C / G / D - B / G / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/F = C / G / D / A - B / G / D / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = C / G / D / A * F - B / G / D / A * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_200", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_200", "raw/question": "D = F - A + G * x * B + C", "raw/answer": "x = D / G / B - F / G / B + A / G / B - C / G / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - A + G * x * B + C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A + G * x * B + C = D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "G * x * B + C = D - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G * x * B = D - F + A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * B = D / G - F / G + A / G - C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = D / G / B - F / G / B + A / G / B - C / G / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_201", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_201", "raw/question": "A - D + x * F * G * C * B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - A / F / G / C / B + D / F / G / C / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D + x * F * G * C * B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x * F * G * C * B = - A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * G * C * B = - A / F + D / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * C * B = - A / F / G + D / F / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * B = - A / F / G / C + D / F / G / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = - A / F / G / C / B + D / F / G / C / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_202", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_202", "raw/question": "F / A - C + D - B / G * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / A * G / B -  C * G / B + D * G / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F / A to the right side", "equation": "- C + D - B / G * x = - F / A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "D - B / G * x = - F / A + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B / G * x = - F / A + C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / G * x = F / A -  C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "B * x = F / A * G -  C * G + D * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = F / A * G / B -  C * G / B + D * G / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_203", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_203", "raw/question": "- B * A / x + G / D + F - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (G / D / B + F / B -  C / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G / D to the right side", "equation": "- B * A / x + F - C = - G / D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B * A / x - C = - G / D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B * A / x = - G / D - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * A / x = G / D + F -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "A/x = G / D / B + F / B -  C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (G / D / B + F / B -  C / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_204", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_204", "raw/question": "C / D * F / x - B + G + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (B * D / C - G * D / C - A * D / C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "C / D * F / x + G + A = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C / D * F / x + A = B - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C / D * F / x = B - G - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C * F/x = B * D - G * D - A * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "F/x = B * D / C - G * D / C - A * D / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (B * D / C - G * D / C - A * D / C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_205", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_205", "raw/question": "C = B + G - F + D - A + x", "raw/answer": "x = C - B - G + F - D + A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + G - F + D - A + x = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G - F + D - A + x = C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- F + D - A + x = C - B - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "D - A + x = C - B - G + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A + x = C - B - G + F - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x = C - B - G + F - D + A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_206", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_206", "raw/question": "- G = C / B - D - F - x - A", "raw/answer": "x = G + C / B -  D -  F -  A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C / B - D - F - x - A = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C / B to the right side", "equation": "- D - F - x - A = - G - C / B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F - x - A = - G - C / B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x - A = - G - C / B + D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x = - G - C / B + D + F + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = G + C / B -  D -  F -  A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_207", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_207", "raw/question": "- G = D - C - B / x * F * A", "raw/answer": "x = B / (G / F / A + D / F / A -  C / F / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - C - B / x * F * A = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - B / x * F * A = - G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B / x * F * A = - G - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / x * F * A = G + D -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "B/x * A = G / F + D / F -  C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "B/x = G / F / A + D / F / A -  C / F / A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (G / F / A + D / F / A -  C / F / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_208", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_208", "raw/question": "A - C - x + B / F - D + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A -  C + B / F -  D + G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - x + B / F - D + G = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x + B / F - D + G = - A + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B / F to the right side", "equation": "- x - D + G = - A + C - B / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + G = - A + C - B / F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - A + C - B / F + D - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = A -  C + B / F -  D + G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_209", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_209", "raw/question": "A - C + D - F - B / G * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A * G / B -  C * G / B + D * G / B -  F * G / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C + D - F - B / G * x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "D - F - B / G * x = - A + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F - B / G * x = - A + C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- B / G * x = - A + C - D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / G * x = A -  C + D -  F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "B * x = A * G -  C * G + D * G -  F * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = A * G / B -  C * G / B + D * G / B -  F * G / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_210", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_210", "raw/question": "- F - D + C * B + G - x * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F / A -  D / A + C * B / A + G / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D + C * B + G - x * A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "C * B + G - x * A = F + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C * B to the right side", "equation": "G - x * A = F + D - C * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = F + D - C * B - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  F -  D + C * B + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F / A -  D / A + C * B / A + G / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_211", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_211", "raw/question": "B + C - D * A + F - G - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B + C -  D * A + F -  G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "C - D * A + F - G - x = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- D * A + F - G - x = - B - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D * A to the right side", "equation": "F - G - x = - B - C + D * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- G - x = - B - C + D * A - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B - C + D * A - F + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B + C -  D * A + F -  G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_212", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_212", "raw/question": "F = C - A * x / B / G + D", "raw/answer": "x = - F / A * G * B + C / A * G * B + D / A * G * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - A * x / B / G + D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A * x / B / G + D = F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A * x / B / G = F - C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x / B / G = - F + C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/B/G = - F / A + C / A + D / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x/B = - F / A * G + C / A * G + D / A * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = - F / A * G * B + C / A * G * B + D / A * G * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_213", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_213", "raw/question": "- F * x / G / D * A / C - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / F * C / A * D * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F * x / G / D * A / C = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x / G / D * A / C = -  B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/G/D * A/C = -  B / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x/G/D * A = -  B / F * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/G/D = -  B / F * C / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/G = -  B / F * C / A * D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / F * C / A * D * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_214", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_214", "raw/question": "- F + D * C - B / A / x - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (-  F * A + D * C * A -  G * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "D * C - B / A / x - G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D * C to the right side", "equation": "- B / A / x - G = F - D * C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- B / A / x = F - D * C + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / A / x = -  F + D * C -  G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "B/ x = -  F * A + D * C * A -  G * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (-  F * A + D * C * A -  G * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_215", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_215", "raw/question": "G - F + A * C - D - B * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / B -  F / B + A * C / B -  D / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- F + A * C - D - B * x = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "A * C - D - B * x = - G + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A * C to the right side", "equation": "- D - B * x = - G + F - A * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B * x = - G + F - A * C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x = G -  F + A * C -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = G / B -  F / B + A * C / B -  D / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_216", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_216", "raw/question": "- C = B * G / x / A - F + D", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- C / B * A + F / B * A - D / B * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B * G / x / A - F + D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "B * G / x / A + D = - C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B * G / x / A = - C + F - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "G/x/A = - C / B + F / B - D / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "G/x = - C / B * A + F / B * A - D / B * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- C / B * A + F / B * A - D / B * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_217", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_217", "raw/question": "B = F + x + D - C + A + G", "raw/answer": "x = B - F - D + C - A - G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + x + D - C + A + G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x + D - C + A + G = B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x - C + A + G = B - F - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x + A + G = B - F - D + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x + G = B - F - D + C - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = B - F - D + C - A - G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_218", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_218", "raw/question": "- G * x + C - F + B + A - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / G -  F / G + B / G + A / G -  D / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x - F + B + A - D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + B + A - D = - C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + A - D = - C + F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x - D = - C + F - B - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- G * x = - C + F - B - A + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x = C -  F + B + A -  D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = C / G -  F / G + B / G + A / G -  D / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_219", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_219", "raw/question": "- D + C = F - A * B / G / x", "raw/answer": "x = B / (D / A * G - C / A * G + F / A * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - A * B / G / x = - D + C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A * B / G / x = - D + C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * B / G / x = D - C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "B/G/x = D / A - C / A + F / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "B/ x = D / A * G - C / A * G + F / A * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (D / A * G - C / A * G + F / A * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_220", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_220", "raw/question": "- D + G - A * B / F * x * C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / A * F / B / C + G / A * F / B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "G - A * B / F * x * C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- A * B / F * x * C = D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * B / F * x * C = -  D + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "B/F * x * C = -  D / A + G / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "B * x * C = -  D / A * F + G / A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * C = -  D / A * F / B + G / A * F / B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / A * F / B / C + G / A * F / B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_221", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_221", "raw/question": "- G + D * A - x * C - B + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G / C + D * A / C -  B / C + F / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "D * A - x * C - B + F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D * A to the right side", "equation": "- x * C - B + F = G - D * A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x * C + F = G - D * A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * C = G - D * A + B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * C = -  G + D * A -  B + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G / C + D * A / C -  B / C + F / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_222", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_222", "raw/question": "D = A + G * C + F - x - B", "raw/answer": "x = - D + A + G * C + F -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + G * C + F - x - B = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G * C + F - x - B = D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G * C to the right side", "equation": "F - x - B = D - A - G * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = D - A - G * C - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = D - A - G * C - F + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - D + A + G * C + F -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_223", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_223", "raw/question": "- C * x * D * A / B + F + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / C / D * B / A + G / C / D * B / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C * x * D * A / B + G = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C * x * D * A / B = - F - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x * D * A / B = F + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * D * A/B = F / C + G / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A/B = F / C / D + G / C / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * A = F / C / D * B + G / C / D * B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = F / C / D * B / A + G / C / D * B / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_224", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_224", "raw/question": "A = G - D - x / C * B / F", "raw/answer": "x = - A * F / B * C + G * F / B * C -  D * F / B * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - D - x / C * B / F = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D - x / C * B / F = A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / C * B / F = A - G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C * B / F = - A + G -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/C * B = - A * F + G * F -  D * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/C = - A * F / B + G * F / B -  D * F / B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = - A * F / B * C + G * F / B * C -  D * F / B * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_225", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_225", "raw/question": "G + C + B + D - A - x - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G + C + B + D -  A -  F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C + B + D - A - x - F = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B + D - A - x - F = - G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D - A - x - F = - G - C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A - x - F = - G - C - B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x - F = - G - C - B - D + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - G - C - B - D + A + F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = G + C + B + D -  A -  F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_226", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_226", "raw/question": "- G = F - C - B * D - A - x", "raw/answer": "x = G + F -  C -  B * D -  A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - C - B * D - A - x = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C - B * D - A - x = - G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B * D - A - x = - G - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B * D to the right side", "equation": "- A - x = - G - F + C + B * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x = - G - F + C + B * D + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = G + F -  C -  B * D -  A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_227", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_227", "raw/question": "- C + F - B * G * D * x * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C / B / G / D / A + F / B / G / D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "F - B * G * D * x * A = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B * G * D * x * A = C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * G * D * x * A = -  C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "G * D * x * A = -  C / B + F / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "D * x * A = -  C / B / G + F / B / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  C / B / G / D + F / B / G / D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C / B / G / D / A + F / B / G / D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_228", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_228", "raw/question": "A = B + F - D - x + G + C", "raw/answer": "x = - A + B + F -  D + G + C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + F - D - x + G + C = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F - D - x + G + C = A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D - x + G + C = A - B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + G + C = A - B - F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x + C = A - B - F + D - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x = A - B - F + D - G - C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - A + B + F -  D + G + C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_229", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_229", "raw/question": "- A / F = D - B + G - C / x", "raw/answer": "x = C / (A / F + D -  B + G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - B + G - C / x = - A / F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B + G - C / x = - A / F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G - C / x = - A / F - D + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C / x = - A / F - D + B - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x = A / F + D -  B + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (A / F + D -  B + G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_230", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_230", "raw/question": "D = A + G + F - x / B + C", "raw/answer": "x = - D * B + A * B + G * B + F * B + C * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + G + F - x / B + C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G + F - x / B + C = D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "F - x / B + C = D - A - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + C = D - A - G - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = D - A - G - F - C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = - D + A + G + F + C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = - D * B + A * B + G * B + F * B + C * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_231", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_231", "raw/question": "- A = F - B + D + C / x - G", "raw/answer": "x = C / (- A - F + B - D + G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - B + D + C / x - G = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B + D + C / x - G = - A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "D + C / x - G = - A - F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "C / x - G = - A - F + B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "C / x = - A - F + B - D + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (- A - F + B - D + G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_232", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_232", "raw/question": "- F * C / B * x + D / A - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / A / F * B / C -  G / F * B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D / A to the right side", "equation": "- F * C / B * x - G = - D / A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- F * C / B * x = - D / A + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * C / B * x = D / A -  G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "C/B * x = D / A / F -  G / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "C * x = D / A / F * B -  G / F * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = D / A / F * B / C -  G / F * B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_233", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_233", "raw/question": "G * D / x - B - F + A + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (B / G + F / G - A / G - C / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G * D / x - F + A + C = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "G * D / x + A + C = B + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G * D / x + C = B + F - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G * D / x = B + F - A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "D/x = B / G + F / G - A / G - C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (B / G + F / G - A / G - C / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_234", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_234", "raw/question": "- G + F - C * A * x + B - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G / C / A + F / C / A + B / C / A -  D / C / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "F - C * A * x + B - D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C * A * x + B - D = G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C * A * x - D = G - F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- C * A * x = G - F - B + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * A * x = -  G + F + B -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "A * x = -  G / C + F / C + B / C -  D / C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G / C / A + F / C / A + B / C / A -  D / C / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_235", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_235", "raw/question": "- G * x / C / B / A + D - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / G * A * B * C -  F / G * A * B * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / C / B / A - F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / C / B / A = - D + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x / C / B / A = D -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/C/B/A = D / G -  F / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/C/B = D / G * A -  F / G * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/C = D / G * A * B -  F / G * A * B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = D / G * A * B * C -  F / G * A * B * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_236", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_236", "raw/question": "- D * A - G * x / C / B + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D * A / G * B * C + F / G * B * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D * A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / C / B + F = D * A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / C / B = D * A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x / C / B = -  D * A + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/C/B = -  D * A / G + F / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/C = -  D * A / G * B + F / G * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D * A / G * B * C + F / G * B * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_237", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_237", "raw/question": "- F - A - B - x / G + D = C", "raw/answer": "x = - C * G -  F * G -  A * G -  B * G + D * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- A - B - x / G + D = C + F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B - x / G + D = C + F + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / G + D = C + F + A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / G = C + F + A + B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G = - C -  F -  A -  B + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = - C * G -  F * G -  A * G -  B * G + D * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_238", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_238", "raw/question": "- B - C * G * x * D - A + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / C / G / D -  A / C / G / D + F / C / G / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C * G * x * D - A + F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C * G * x * D + F = B + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C * G * x * D = B + A - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * G * x * D = -  B -  A + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "G * x * D = -  B / C -  A / C + F / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * D = -  B / C / G -  A / C / G + F / C / G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / C / G / D -  A / C / G / D + F / C / G / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_239", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_239", "raw/question": "A - G * x + C - F + D * B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / G + C / G -  F / G + D * B / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + C - F + D * B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x - F + D * B = - A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + D * B = - A - C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D * B to the right side", "equation": "- G * x = - A - C + F - D * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x = A + C -  F + D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = A / G + C / G -  F / G + D * B / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_240", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_240", "raw/question": "D - C - F * x - A + G * B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / F -  C / F -  A / F + G * B / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - F * x - A + G * B = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F * x - A + G * B = - D + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- F * x + G * B = - D + C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G * B to the right side", "equation": "- F * x = - D + C + A - G * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x = D -  C -  A + G * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = D / F -  C / F -  A / F + G * B / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_241", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_241", "raw/question": "- B = F * A - C * x - D + G", "raw/answer": "x = B / C + F * A / C -  D / C + G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F * A - C * x - D + G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F * A to the right side", "equation": "- C * x - D + G = - B - F * A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- C * x + G = - B - F * A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C * x = - B - F * A + D - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x = B + F * A -  D + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / C + F * A / C -  D / C + G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_242", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_242", "raw/question": "D + A - x / B + F + G - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D * B + A * B + F * B + G * B -  C * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "A - x / B + F + G - C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + F + G - C = - D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B + G - C = - D - A - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x / B - C = - D - A - F - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = - D - A - F - G + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = D + A + F + G -  C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = D * B + A * B + F * B + G * B -  C * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_243", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_243", "raw/question": "- F * x / A * B / G / C = D", "raw/answer": "x = - D / F * C * G / B * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x / A * B / G / C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/A * B/G/C = - D / F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x/A * B/G = - D / F * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x/A * B = - D / F * C * G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/A = - D / F * C * G / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / F * C * G / B * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_244", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_244", "raw/question": "- G - x * A * C - D - B / F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G / A / C -  D / A / C -  B / F / A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x * A * C - D - B / F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * A * C - B / F = G + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B / F to the right side", "equation": "- x * A * C = G + D + B / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A * C = -  G -  D -  B / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * C = -  G / A -  D / A -  B / F / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G / A / C -  D / A / C -  B / F / A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_245", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_245", "raw/question": "F - B = A - G * C / x - D", "raw/answer": "x = C / (- F / G + B / G + A / G -  D / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - G * C / x - D = F - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * C / x - D = F - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- G * C / x = F - B - A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * C / x = - F + B + A -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "C/x = - F / G + B / G + A / G -  D / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (- F / G + B / G + A / G -  D / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_246", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_246", "raw/question": "D - C - F - x + G + A = B", "raw/answer": "x = - B + D -  C -  F + G + A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - F - x + G + A = B - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F - x + G + A = B - D + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x + G + A = B - D + C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x + A = B - D + C + F - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x = B - D + C + F - G - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - B + D -  C -  F + G + A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_247", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_247", "raw/question": "- B - A * D - x + G - F - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B -  A * D + G -  F -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A * D - x + G - F - C = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A * D to the right side", "equation": "- x + G - F - C = B + A * D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - F - C = B + A * D - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x - C = B + A * D - G + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = B + A * D - G + F + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B -  A * D + G -  F -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_248", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_248", "raw/question": "- F = G / C * x / A + D - B", "raw/answer": "x = - F * C / G * A - D * C / G * A + B * C / G * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G / C * x / A + D - B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "G / C * x / A - B = - F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G / C * x / A = - F - D + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "G * x/A = - F * C - D * C + B * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/A = - F * C / G - D * C / G + B * C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * C / G * A - D * C / G * A + B * C / G * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_249", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_249", "raw/question": "- G = A - D / x / B + C * F", "raw/answer": "x = D / (G * B + A * B + C * F * B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - D / x / B + C * F = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D / x / B + C * F = - G - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C * F to the right side", "equation": "- D / x / B = - G - A - C * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x / B = G + A + C * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "D/x = G * B + A * B + C * F * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (G * B + A * B + C * F * B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_250", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_250", "raw/question": "- C = x - D + B + G + A - F", "raw/answer": "x = - C + D - B - G - A + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x - D + B + G + A - F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x + B + G + A - F = - C + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x + G + A - F = - C + D - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x + A - F = - C + D - B - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x - F = - C + D - B - G - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x = - C + D - B - G - A + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_251", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_251", "raw/question": "- C - F - D - x + A + B + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C -  F -  D + A + B + G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F - D - x + A + B + G = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D - x + A + B + G = C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + A + B + G = C + F + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x + B + G = C + F + D - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x + G = C + F + D - A - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x = C + F + D - A - B - G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C -  F -  D + A + B + G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_252", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_252", "raw/question": "D = x * F - G - B + A - C", "raw/answer": "x = D / F + G / F + B / F - A / F + C / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x * F - G - B + A - C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x * F - B + A - C = D + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "x * F + A - C = D + G + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x * F - C = D + G + B - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x * F = D + G + B - A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = D / F + G / F + B / F - A / F + C / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_253", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_253", "raw/question": "D - x / C / G - A + B - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D * G * C -  A * G * C + B * G * C -  F * G * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / C / G - A + B - F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / C / G + B - F = - D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / C / G - F = - D + A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / C / G = - D + A - B + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C / G = D -  A + B -  F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x/C = D * G -  A * G + B * G -  F * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = D * G * C -  A * G * C + B * G * C -  F * G * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_254", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_254", "raw/question": "- B = G - D / x + F - C / A", "raw/answer": "x = D / (B + G + F -  C / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - D / x + F - C / A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D / x + F - C / A = - B - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D / x - C / A = - B - G - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C / A to the right side", "equation": "- D / x = - B - G - F + C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x = B + G + F -  C / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (B + G + F -  C / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_255", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_255", "raw/question": "- C - A = G - D / B * x * F", "raw/answer": "x = C * B / D / F + A * B / D / F + G * B / D / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - D / B * x * F = - C - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D / B * x * F = - C - A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / B * x * F = C + A + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "D * x * F = C * B + A * B + G * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * F = C * B / D + A * B / D + G * B / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = C * B / D / F + A * B / D / F + G * B / D / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_256", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_256", "raw/question": "- G = B - A - D + F + x + C", "raw/answer": "x = - G - B + A + D - F - C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - A - D + F + x + C = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A - D + F + x + C = - G - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D + F + x + C = - G - B + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "F + x + C = - G - B + A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x + C = - G - B + A + D - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = - G - B + A + D - F - C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_257", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_257", "raw/question": "- F = A + B - x * G - C * D", "raw/answer": "x = F / G + A / G + B / G -  C * D / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + B - x * G - C * D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "B - x * G - C * D = - F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * G - C * D = - F - A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C * D to the right side", "equation": "- x * G = - F - A - B + C * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G = F + A + B -  C * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = F / G + A / G + B / G -  C * D / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_258", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_258", "raw/question": "D = A - C - B - G / x - F", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- D + A -  C -  B -  F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - C - B - G / x - F = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - B - G / x - F = D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B - G / x - F = D - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G / x - F = D - A + C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G / x = D - A + C + B + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / x = - D + A -  C -  B -  F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- D + A -  C -  B -  F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_259", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_259", "raw/question": "- A = F / C + B - G - D - x", "raw/answer": "x = A + F / C + B -  G -  D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F / C + B - G - D - x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F / C to the right side", "equation": "B - G - D - x = - A - F / C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G - D - x = - A - F / C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- D - x = - A - F / C - B + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - A - F / C - B + G + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = A + F / C + B -  G -  D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_260", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_260", "raw/question": "B + D * x / A / C + F - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - B / D * C * A - F / D * C * A + G / D * C * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D * x / A / C + F - G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D * x / A / C - G = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "D * x / A / C = - B - F + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/A/C = - B / D - F / D + G / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x/A = - B / D * C - F / D * C + G / D * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / D * C * A - F / D * C * A + G / D * C * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_261", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_261", "raw/question": "- F / G * C / D / x / A = B", "raw/answer": "x = C / (- B * G / F * A * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / G * C / D / x / A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "F * C/D/x/A = - B * G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "C/D/x/A = - B * G / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C/D/x = - B * G / F * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/ x = - B * G / F * A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (- B * G / F * A * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_262", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_262", "raw/question": "G + B - x / A * C / D * F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G * D / C / F * A + B * D / C / F * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "B - x / A * C / D * F = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A * C / D * F = - G - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A * C / D * F = G + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/A * C * F = G * D + B * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/A * F = G * D / C + B * D / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/A = G * D / C / F + B * D / C / F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = G * D / C / F * A + B * D / C / F * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_263", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_263", "raw/question": "B - D - x / A * F / G = C", "raw/answer": "x = - C * G / F * A + B * G / F * A -  D * G / F * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D - x / A * F / G = C - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / A * F / G = C - B + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A * F / G = - C + B -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x/A * F = - C * G + B * G -  D * G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/A = - C * G / F + B * G / F -  D * G / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - C * G / F * A + B * G / F * A -  D * G / F * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_264", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_264", "raw/question": "- C - G - A - x + F - D * B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C -  G -  A + F -  D * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- G - A - x + F - D * B = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- A - x + F - D * B = C + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + F - D * B = C + G + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x - D * B = C + G + A - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D * B to the right side", "equation": "- x = C + G + A - F + D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C -  G -  A + F -  D * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_265", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_265", "raw/question": "- B + A = G - D - x * F * C", "raw/answer": "x = B / F / C - A / F / C + G / F / C -  D / F / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - D - x * F * C = - B + A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D - x * F * C = - B + A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * F * C = - B + A - G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F * C = B - A + G -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * C = B / F - A / F + G / F -  D / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / F / C - A / F / C + G / F / C -  D / F / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_266", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_266", "raw/question": "D * A = F - C - G * x - B", "raw/answer": "x = - D * A / G + F / G -  C / G -  B / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - C - G * x - B = D * A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C - G * x - B = D * A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x - B = D * A - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G * x = D * A - F + C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x = - D * A + F -  C -  B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - D * A / G + F / G -  C / G -  B / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_267", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_267", "raw/question": "- G = A * D - B / F * x - C", "raw/answer": "x = G * F / B + A * D * F / B -  C * F / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A * D - B / F * x - C = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A * D to the right side", "equation": "- B / F * x - C = - G - A * D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B / F * x = - G - A * D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / F * x = G + A * D -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "B * x = G * F + A * D * F -  C * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = G * F / B + A * D * F / B -  C * F / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_268", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_268", "raw/question": "A * D / x + G - C + B + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (- G / A + C / A - B / A - F / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x - C + B + F = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x + B + F = - G + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x + F = - G + C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x = - G + C - B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "D/x = - G / A + C / A - B / A - F / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (- G / A + C / A - B / A - F / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_269", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_269", "raw/question": "- B = D * A + G - C - x / F", "raw/answer": "x = B * F + D * A * F + G * F -  C * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D * A + G - C - x / F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D * A to the right side", "equation": "G - C - x / F = - B - D * A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C - x / F = - B - D * A - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F = - B - D * A - G + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F = B + D * A + G -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = B * F + D * A * F + G * F -  C * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_270", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_270", "raw/question": "- A = x * C - B - D - F - G", "raw/answer": "x = - A / C + B / C + D / C + F / C + G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x * C - B - D - F - G = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "x * C - D - F - G = - A + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x * C - F - G = - A + B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x * C - G = - A + B + D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x * C = - A + B + D + F + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = - A / C + B / C + D / C + F / C + G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_271", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_271", "raw/question": "- A + F = B - C / x / D * G", "raw/answer": "x = C / (A / G * D - F / G * D + B / G * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - C / x / D * G = - A + F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C / x / D * G = - A + F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x / D * G = A - F + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "C/x/D = A / G - F / G + B / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/x = A / G * D - F / G * D + B / G * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (A / G * D - F / G * D + B / G * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_272", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_272", "raw/question": "C + x * D / G * A * B + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - C * G / D / A / B - F * G / D / A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x * D / G * A * B + F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x * D / G * A * B = - C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x * D * A * B = - C * G - F * G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A * B = - C * G / D - F * G / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * B = - C * G / D / A - F * G / D / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = - C * G / D / A / B - F * G / D / A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_273", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_273", "raw/question": "- A / C / x / B / F - G - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (-  G * F * B * C -  D * F * B * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- A / C / x / B / F - D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- A / C / x / B / F = G + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / C / x / B / F = -  G -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "A/C/x/B = -  G * F -  D * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "A/C/x = -  G * F * B -  D * F * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "A/ x = -  G * F * B * C -  D * F * B * C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (-  G * F * B * C -  D * F * B * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_274", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_274", "raw/question": "- D = G + A - C * x * B / F", "raw/answer": "x = D / C * F / B + G / C * F / B + A / C * F / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + A - C * x * B / F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "A - C * x * B / F = - D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C * x * B / F = - D - G - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x * B / F = D + G + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * B/F = D / C + G / C + A / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * B = D / C * F + G / C * F + A / C * F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = D / C * F / B + G / C * F / B + A / C * F / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_275", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_275", "raw/question": "F + C + A + B - D - x - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F + C + A + B -  D -  G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "C + A + B - D - x - G = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "A + B - D - x - G = - F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "B - D - x - G = - F - C - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D - x - G = - F - C - A - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - G = - F - C - A - B + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F - C - A - B + D + G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F + C + A + B -  D -  G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_276", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_276", "raw/question": "B = A + D * x + C + F - G", "raw/answer": "x = B / D - A / D - C / D - F / D + G / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + D * x + C + F - G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D * x + C + F - G = B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "D * x + F - G = B - A - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D * x - G = B - A - C - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "D * x = B - A - C - F + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = B / D - A / D - C / D - F / D + G / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_277", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_277", "raw/question": "- A = x - F + G + B - C + D", "raw/answer": "x = - A + F - G - B + C - D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x - F + G + B - C + D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x + G + B - C + D = - A + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x + B - C + D = - A + F - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x - C + D = - A + F - G - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x + D = - A + F - G - B + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = - A + F - G - B + C - D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_278", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_278", "raw/question": "G / A = C - x * B + D + F", "raw/answer": "x = - G / A / B + C / B + D / B + F / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - x * B + D + F = G / A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * B + D + F = G / A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * B + F = G / A - C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * B = G / A - C - D - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B = - G / A + C + D + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = - G / A / B + C / B + D / B + F / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_279", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_279", "raw/question": "- x / D / A * G / C + F - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F * C / G * A * D -  B * C / G * A * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / D / A * G / C - B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / D / A * G / C = - F + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D / A * G / C = F -  B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x/D/A * G = F * C -  B * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/D/A = F * C / G -  B * C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/D = F * C / G * A -  B * C / G * A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = F * C / G * A * D -  B * C / G * A * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_280", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_280", "raw/question": "- G / A / x * D + C - F = B", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- B / D * A + C / D * A -  F / D * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G / A / x * D - F = B - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G / A / x * D = B - C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / A / x * D = - B + C -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "G/A/x = - B / D + C / D -  F / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "G/ x = - B / D * A + C / D * A -  F / D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- B / D * A + C / D * A -  F / D * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_281", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_281", "raw/question": "- x + F + C / D - G + A - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F + C / D -  G + A -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x + C / D - G + A - B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C / D to the right side", "equation": "- x - G + A - B = - F - C / D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x + A - B = - F - C / D + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = - F - C / D + G - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F - C / D + G - A + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F + C / D -  G + A -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_282", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_282", "raw/question": "F = G * C * B * x * D / A", "raw/answer": "x = F / G / C / B * A / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G * C * B * x * D / A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "C * B * x * D/A = F / G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "B * x * D/A = F / G / C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * D/A = F / G / C / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x * D = F / G / C / B * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = F / G / C / B * A / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_283", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_283", "raw/question": "D = C + G * x - B + F - A", "raw/answer": "x = D / G - C / G + B / G - F / G + A / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C + G * x - B + F - A = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G * x - B + F - A = D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G * x + F - A = D - C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "G * x - A = D - C + B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "G * x = D - C + B - F + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = D / G - C / G + B / G - F / G + A / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_284", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_284", "raw/question": "- G / x * A + D - B + F * C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / (D / A -  B / A + F * C / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- G / x * A - B + F * C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G / x * A + F * C = - D + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F * C to the right side", "equation": "- G / x * A = - D + B - F * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / x * A = D -  B + F * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "G/x = D / A -  B / A + F * C / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (D / A -  B / A + F * C / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_285", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_285", "raw/question": "F / G + A + B - D / C * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / G * C / D + A * C / D + B * C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F / G to the right side", "equation": "A + B - D / C * x = - F / G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "B - D / C * x = - F / G - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D / C * x = - F / G - A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / C * x = F / G + A + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "D * x = F / G * C + A * C + B * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = F / G * C / D + A * C / D + B * C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_286", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_286", "raw/question": "D * x + A + B - C + F + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - A / D - B / D + C / D - F / D - G / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D * x + B - C + F + G = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D * x - C + F + G = - A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "D * x + F + G = - A - B + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D * x + G = - A - B + C - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "D * x = - A - B + C - F - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = - A / D - B / D + C / D - F / D - G / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_287", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_287", "raw/question": "- A / B = F - C / x * G + D", "raw/answer": "x = C / (A / B / G + F / G + D / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - C / x * G + D = - A / B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * G + D = - A / B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * G = - A / B - F - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x * G = A / B + F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "C/x = A / B / G + F / G + D / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (A / B / G + F / G + D / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_288", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_288", "raw/question": "F - D = C + B - G * A / x", "raw/answer": "x = A / (- F / G + D / G + C / G + B / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C + B - G * A / x = F - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B - G * A / x = F - D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G * A / x = F - D - C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * A / x = - F + D + C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "A/x = - F / G + D / G + C / G + B / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (- F / G + D / G + C / G + B / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_289", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_289", "raw/question": "- C * A - G / x / D * F - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / (-  C * A / F * D -  B / F * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C * A to the right side", "equation": "- G / x / D * F - B = C * A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G / x / D * F = C * A + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / x / D * F = -  C * A -  B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "G/x/D = -  C * A / F -  B / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "G/x = -  C * A / F * D -  B / F * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (-  C * A / F * D -  B / F * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_290", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_290", "raw/question": "- A = F / B / x / D / G / C", "raw/answer": "x = F / (- A * C * G * D * B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F / B / x / D / G / C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "F/B/x/D/G = - A * C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "F/B/x/D = - A * C * G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "F/B/x = - A * C * G * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "F/ x = - A * C * G * D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (- A * C * G * D * B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_291", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_291", "raw/question": "- x * D / C - B * F - A + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B * F * C / D -  A * C / D + G * C / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B * F to the right side", "equation": "- x * D / C - A + G = B * F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x * D / C + G = B * F + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x * D / C = B * F + A - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * D / C = -  B * F -  A + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x * D = -  B * F * C -  A * C + G * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B * F * C / D -  A * C / D + G * C / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_292", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_292", "raw/question": "F + D * C + B - A / x / G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (F * G + D * C * G + B * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D * C + B - A / x / G = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D * C to the right side", "equation": "B - A / x / G = - F - D * C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A / x / G = - F - D * C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / x / G = F + D * C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "A/x = F * G + D * C * G + B * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (F * G + D * C * G + B * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_293", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_293", "raw/question": "- B + G * C - x + F - D - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B + G * C + F -  D -  A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G * C - x + F - D - A = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G * C to the right side", "equation": "- x + F - D - A = B - G * C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - A = B - G * C - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - A = B - G * C - F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x = B - G * C - F + D + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B + G * C + F -  D -  A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_294", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_294", "raw/question": "B / F + G + A - C / x - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (B / F + G + A -  D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B / F to the right side", "equation": "G + A - C / x - D = - B / F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "A - C / x - D = - B / F - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C / x - D = - B / F - G - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- C / x = - B / F - G - A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x = B / F + G + A -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (B / F + G + A -  D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_295", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_295", "raw/question": "- G - D * x * F + C - A = B", "raw/answer": "x = - B / D / F -  G / D / F + C / D / F -  A / D / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- D * x * F + C - A = B + G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- D * x * F - A = B + G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D * x * F = B + G - C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * x * F = - B -  G + C -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * F = - B / D -  G / D + C / D -  A / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / D / F -  G / D / F + C / D / F -  A / D / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_296", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_296", "raw/question": "- F = A / B - x * G * C + D", "raw/answer": "x = F / G / C + A / B / G / C + D / G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A / B - x * G * C + D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A / B to the right side", "equation": "- x * G * C + D = - F - A / B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * G * C = - F - A / B - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G * C = F + A / B + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * C = F / G + A / B / G + D / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = F / G / C + A / B / G / C + D / G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_297", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_297", "raw/question": "A + C + D / x + G + F + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (- A - C - G - F - B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C + D / x + G + F + B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "D / x + G + F + B = - A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "D / x + F + B = - A - C - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D / x + B = - A - C - G - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D / x = - A - C - G - F - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (- A - C - G - F - B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_298", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_298", "raw/question": "- A = F + C / B - D / x - G", "raw/answer": "x = D / (A + F + C / B -  G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + C / B - D / x - G = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "C / B - D / x - G = - A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C / B to the right side", "equation": "- D / x - G = - A - F - C / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- D / x = - A - F - C / B + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x = A + F + C / B -  G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (A + F + C / B -  G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_299", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_299", "raw/question": "- G = A + F - B / D - C - x", "raw/answer": "x = G + A + F -  B / D -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + F - B / D - C - x = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "F - B / D - C - x = - G - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B / D - C - x = - G - A - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B / D to the right side", "equation": "- C - x = - G - A - F + B / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = - G - A - F + B / D + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = G + A + F -  B / D -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_300", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_300", "raw/question": "- D + F * x * B * C - A + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / F / B / C + A / F / B / C - G / F / B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "F * x * B * C - A + G = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "F * x * B * C + G = D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "F * x * B * C = D + A - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * B * C = D / F + A / F - G / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * C = D / F / B + A / F / B - G / F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = D / F / B / C + A / F / B / C - G / F / B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_301", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_301", "raw/question": "- A + G - C - x - F / D - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A + G -  C -  F / D -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "G - C - x - F / D - B = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C - x - F / D - B = A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - F / D - B = A - G + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F / D to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = A - G + C + F / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = A - G + C + F / D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A + G -  C -  F / D -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_302", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_302", "raw/question": "- B / x - C - A - F * D - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (-  C -  A -  F * D -  G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B / x - A - F * D - G = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B / x - F * D - G = C + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F * D to the right side", "equation": "- B / x - G = C + A + F * D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- B / x = C + A + F * D + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / x = -  C -  A -  F * D -  G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (-  C -  A -  F * D -  G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_303", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_303", "raw/question": "- A + B / D * x * G - C + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A * D / B / G + C * D / B / G - F * D / B / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "B / D * x * G - C + F = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "B / D * x * G + F = A + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "B / D * x * G = A + C - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "B * x * G = A * D + C * D - F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * G = A * D / B + C * D / B - F * D / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = A * D / B / G + C * D / B / G - F * D / B / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_304", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_304", "raw/question": "- C - D - F * B + A + G - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C -  D -  F * B + A + G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- D - F * B + A + G - x = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * B + A + G - x = C + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F * B to the right side", "equation": "A + G - x = C + D + F * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G - x = C + D + F * B - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x = C + D + F * B - A - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C -  D -  F * B + A + G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_305", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_305", "raw/question": "C + B - D - x * A - G * F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / A + B / A -  D / A -  G * F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B - D - x * A - G * F = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D - x * A - G * F = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * A - G * F = - C - B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G * F to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = - C - B + D + G * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = C + B -  D -  G * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C / A + B / A -  D / A -  G * F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_306", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_306", "raw/question": "D - x - F * B - C - A + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D -  F * B -  C -  A + G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x - F * B - C - A + G = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F * B to the right side", "equation": "- x - C - A + G = - D + F * B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - A + G = - D + F * B + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + G = - D + F * B + C + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - D + F * B + C + A - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = D -  F * B -  C -  A + G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_307", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_307", "raw/question": "B / C = F - G * x / D * A", "raw/answer": "x = - B / C / G / A * D + F / G / A * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - G * x / D * A = B / C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / D * A = B / C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x / D * A = - B / C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/D * A = - B / C / G + F / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/D = - B / C / G / A + F / G / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / C / G / A * D + F / G / A * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_308", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_308", "raw/question": "B = A * D / x - C - F + G", "raw/answer": "x = D / (B / A + C / A + F / A - G / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A * D / x - C - F + G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x - F + G = B + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x + G = B + C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x = B + C + F - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "D/x = B / A + C / A + F / A - G / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (B / A + C / A + F / A - G / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_309", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_309", "raw/question": "D + A * G * F / B * x / C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - D / A / G * B / F * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "A * G * F / B * x / C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "G * F/B * x/C = - D / A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "F/B * x/C = - D / A / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "F * x/C = - D / A / G * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/C = - D / A / G * B / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / A / G * B / F * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_310", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_310", "raw/question": "G + C - x + A + F / D + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G + C + A + F / D + B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C - x + A + F / D + B = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x + A + F / D + B = - G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x + F / D + B = - G - C - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F / D to the right side", "equation": "- x + B = - G - C - A - F / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x = - G - C - A - F / D - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = G + C + A + F / D + B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_311", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_311", "raw/question": "- A = F / x * B / C + D + G", "raw/answer": "x = F / (- A * C / B - D * C / B - G * C / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F / x * B / C + D + G = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F / x * B / C + G = - A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "F / x * B / C = - A - D - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "F/x * B = - A * C - D * C - G * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "F/x = - A * C / B - D * C / B - G * C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (- A * C / B - D * C / B - G * C / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_312", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_312", "raw/question": "x + C + B - F - D - A + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - C - B + F + D + A - G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x + B - F - D - A + G = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x - F - D - A + G = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x - D - A + G = - C - B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x - A + G = - C - B + F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x + G = - C - B + F + D + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = - C - B + F + D + A - G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_313", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_313", "raw/question": "- A = F + D * G / C / B / x", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- A / D * B * C - F / D * B * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + D * G / C / B / x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D * G / C / B / x = - A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "G/C/B/x = - A / D - F / D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "G/C/ x = - A / D * B - F / D * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "G/ x = - A / D * B * C - F / D * B * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- A / D * B * C - F / D * B * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_314", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_314", "raw/question": "- D = C - A + G * x / B * F", "raw/answer": "x = - D / G / F * B - C / G / F * B + A / G / F * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - A + G * x / B * F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A + G * x / B * F = - D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "G * x / B * F = - D - C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/B * F = - D / G - C / G + A / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/B = - D / G / F - C / G / F + A / G / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / G / F * B - C / G / F * B + A / G / F * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_315", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_315", "raw/question": "G = A / D / B / C * x - F", "raw/answer": "x = G * C * B * D / A + F * C * B * D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A / D / B / C * x - F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "A / D / B / C * x = G + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "A/D/B * x = G * C + F * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "A/D * x = G * C * B + F * C * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "A * x = G * C * B * D + F * C * B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = G * C * B * D / A + F * C * B * D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_316", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_316", "raw/question": "C + B - G - D / A / x = F", "raw/answer": "x = D / (- F * A + C * A + B * A -  G * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B - G - D / A / x = F - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G - D / A / x = F - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- D / A / x = F - C - B + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / A / x = - F + C + B -  G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "D/ x = - F * A + C * A + B * A -  G * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (- F * A + C * A + B * A -  G * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_317", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_317", "raw/question": "x / A * G / B * C - F + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F * B / G / C * A - D * B / G / C * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x / A * G / B * C + D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x / A * G / B * C = F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/A * G * C = F * B - D * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/A * C = F * B / G - D * B / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/A = F * B / G / C - D * B / G / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = F * B / G / C * A - D * B / G / C * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_318", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_318", "raw/question": "- A = G - D - B - F - x / C", "raw/answer": "x = A * C + G * C -  D * C -  B * C -  F * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - D - B - F - x / C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D - B - F - x / C = - A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B - F - x / C = - A - G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F - x / C = - A - G + D + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / C = - A - G + D + B + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C = A + G -  D -  B -  F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = A * C + G * C -  D * C -  B * C -  F * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_319", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_319", "raw/question": "- B = F - x / G / D + C / A", "raw/answer": "x = B * D * G + F * D * G + C / A * D * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - x / G / D + C / A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / G / D + C / A = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C / A to the right side", "equation": "- x / G / D = - B - F - C / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G / D = B + F + C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/G = B * D + F * D + C / A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = B * D * G + F * D * G + C / A * D * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_320", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_320", "raw/question": "- C * B / x * D / A + G * F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (G * F / C * A / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G * F to the right side", "equation": "- C * B / x * D / A = - G * F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * B / x * D / A = G * F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "B/x * D/A = G * F / C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "B/x * D = G * F / C * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "B/x = G * F / C * A / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (G * F / C * A / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_321", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_321", "raw/question": "- G - x / B / A + C + D * F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G * A * B + C * A * B + D * F * A * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / B / A + C + D * F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / B / A + D * F = G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D * F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B / A = G - C - D * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B / A = -  G + C + D * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/B = -  G * A + C * A + D * F * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G * A * B + C * A * B + D * F * A * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_322", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_322", "raw/question": "A - F + C + B - x * G - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / G -  F / G + C / G + B / G -  D / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F + C + B - x * G - D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "C + B - x * G - D = - A + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B - x * G - D = - A + F - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * G - D = - A + F - C - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * G = - A + F - C - B + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G = A -  F + C + B -  D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = A / G -  F / G + C / G + B / G -  D / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_323", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_323", "raw/question": "- F = A + x / C + G - B - D", "raw/answer": "x = - F * C - A * C - G * C + B * C + D * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + x / C + G - B - D = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x / C + G - B - D = - F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x / C - B - D = - F - A - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "x / C - D = - F - A - G + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x / C = - F - A - G + B + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * C - A * C - G * C + B * C + D * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_324", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_324", "raw/question": "G = A + x / B * D * F * C", "raw/answer": "x = G / D / F / C * B - A / D / F / C * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + x / B * D * F * C = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x / B * D * F * C = G - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/B * F * C = G / D - A / D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/B * C = G / D / F - A / D / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/B = G / D / F / C - A / D / F / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = G / D / F / C * B - A / D / F / C * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_325", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_325", "raw/question": "- B = F - A - C + D - x / G", "raw/answer": "x = B * G + F * G -  A * G -  C * G + D * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - A - C + D - x / G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A - C + D - x / G = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C + D - x / G = - B - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "D - x / G = - B - F + A + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / G = - B - F + A + C - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G = B + F -  A -  C + D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = B * G + F * G -  A * G -  C * G + D * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_326", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_326", "raw/question": "G - A / x + F / C + D - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (G + F / C + D -  B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- A / x + F / C + D - B = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F / C to the right side", "equation": "- A / x + D - B = - G - F / C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A / x - B = - G - F / C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A / x = - G - F / C - D + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / x = G + F / C + D -  B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (G + F / C + D -  B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_327", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_327", "raw/question": "B - x * C - A * D - F - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / C -  A * D / C -  F / C -  G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * C - A * D - F - G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A * D to the right side", "equation": "- x * C - F - G = - B + A * D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x * C - G = - B + A * D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x * C = - B + A * D + F + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * C = B -  A * D -  F -  G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / C -  A * D / C -  F / C -  G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_328", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_328", "raw/question": "D = C + G * B - F * x / A", "raw/answer": "x = - D / F * A + C / F * A + G * B / F * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C + G * B - F * x / A = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G * B - F * x / A = D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G * B to the right side", "equation": "- F * x / A = D - C - G * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x / A = - D + C + G * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/A = - D / F + C / F + G * B / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / F * A + C / F * A + G * B / F * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_329", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_329", "raw/question": "- D = B + G * A - x * F + C", "raw/answer": "x = D / F + B / F + G * A / F + C / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + G * A - x * F + C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G * A - x * F + C = - D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G * A to the right side", "equation": "- x * F + C = - D - B - G * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * F = - D - B - G * A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F = D + B + G * A + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = D / F + B / F + G * A / F + C / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_330", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_330", "raw/question": "- D + A = B + F - x * G * C", "raw/answer": "x = D / G / C - A / G / C + B / G / C + F / G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + F - x * G * C = - D + A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F - x * G * C = - D + A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * G * C = - D + A - B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G * C = D - A + B + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * C = D / G - A / G + B / G + F / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = D / G / C - A / G / C + B / G / C + F / G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_331", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_331", "raw/question": "- G = B - D + C / x / A * F", "raw/answer": "x = C / (- G / F * A - B / F * A + D / F * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - D + C / x / A * F = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D + C / x / A * F = - G - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "C / x / A * F = - G - B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "C/x/A = - G / F - B / F + D / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C/x = - G / F * A - B / F * A + D / F * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (- G / F * A - B / F * A + D / F * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_332", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_332", "raw/question": "- x + B * C - F + G - D + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B * C -  F + G -  D + A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B * C to the right side", "equation": "- x - F + G - D + A = - B * C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x + G - D + A = - B * C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - D + A = - B * C + F - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + A = - B * C + F - G + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B * C + F - G + D - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B * C -  F + G -  D + A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_333", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_333", "raw/question": "B = A - C + D * G / x + F", "raw/answer": "x = G / (B / D - A / D + C / D - F / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - C + D * G / x + F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C + D * G / x + F = B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "D * G / x + F = B - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D * G / x = B - A + C - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "G/x = B / D - A / D + C / D - F / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (B / D - A / D + C / D - F / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_334", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_334", "raw/question": "F - D - A - C * x - G - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / C -  D / C -  A / C -  G / C -  B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D - A - C * x - G - B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- A - C * x - G - B = - F + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C * x - G - B = - F + D + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- C * x - B = - F + D + A + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C * x = - F + D + A + G + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x = F -  D -  A -  G -  B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = F / C -  D / C -  A / C -  G / C -  B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_335", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_335", "raw/question": "- A * D - C / B / F * x - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A * D * F * B / C -  G * F * B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A * D to the right side", "equation": "- C / B / F * x - G = A * D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- C / B / F * x = A * D + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / B / F * x = -  A * D -  G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "C/B * x = -  A * D * F -  G * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "C * x = -  A * D * F * B -  G * F * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A * D * F * B / C -  G * F * B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_336", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_336", "raw/question": "F = A + D - x + G / B - C", "raw/answer": "x = - F + A + D + G / B -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + D - x + G / B - C = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D - x + G / B - C = F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x + G / B - C = F - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G / B to the right side", "equation": "- x - C = F - A - D - G / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = F - A - D - G / B + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - F + A + D + G / B -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_337", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_337", "raw/question": "- A * B / G / x / D - C - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (-  C / A * D * G -  F / A * D * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- A * B / G / x / D - F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- A * B / G / x / D = C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * B / G / x / D = -  C -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "B/G/x/D = -  C / A -  F / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "B/G/x = -  C / A * D -  F / A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "B/ x = -  C / A * D * G -  F / A * D * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (-  C / A * D * G -  F / A * D * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_338", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_338", "raw/question": "- F - B - D + C * A - x / G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F * G -  B * G -  D * G + C * A * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- B - D + C * A - x / G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- D + C * A - x / G = F + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "C * A - x / G = F + B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C * A to the right side", "equation": "- x / G = F + B + D - C * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G = -  F -  B -  D + C * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F * G -  B * G -  D * G + C * A * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_339", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_339", "raw/question": "- B = F + C - x - G + A / D", "raw/answer": "x = B + F + C -  G + A / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + C - x - G + A / D = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "C - x - G + A / D = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - G + A / D = - B - F - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x + A / D = - B - F - C + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A / D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B - F - C + G - A / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B + F + C -  G + A / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_340", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_340", "raw/question": "- D = x - B + A + C + G + F", "raw/answer": "x = - D + B - A - C - G - F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x - B + A + C + G + F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "x + A + C + G + F = - D + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x + C + G + F = - D + B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x + G + F = - D + B - A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x + F = - D + B - A - C - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = - D + B - A - C - G - F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_341", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_341", "raw/question": "x * B * D - A + F - G + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / B / D - F / B / D + G / B / D - C / B / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x * B * D + F - G + C = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x * B * D - G + C = A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x * B * D + C = A - F + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x * B * D = A - F + G - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * D = A / B - F / B + G / B - C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = A / B / D - F / B / D + G / B / D - C / B / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_342", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_342", "raw/question": "B - D / A / x / F * C + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (B / C * F * A + G / C * F * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D / A / x / F * C + G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D / A / x / F * C = - B - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / A / x / F * C = B + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "D/A/x/F = B / C + G / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "D/A/x = B / C * F + G / C * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "D/ x = B / C * F * A + G / C * F * A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (B / C * F * A + G / C * F * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_343", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_343", "raw/question": "B + D - A - G - C / x * F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (B / F + D / F -  A / F -  G / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "D - A - G - C / x * F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A - G - C / x * F = - B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- G - C / x * F = - B - D + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- C / x * F = - B - D + A + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x * F = B + D -  A -  G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "C/x = B / F + D / F -  A / F -  G / F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (B / F + D / F -  A / F -  G / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_344", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_344", "raw/question": "- G - D / B * x - C - A / F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G * B / D -  C * B / D -  A / F * B / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- D / B * x - C - A / F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- D / B * x - A / F = G + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A / F to the right side", "equation": "- D / B * x = G + C + A / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / B * x = -  G -  C -  A / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "D * x = -  G * B -  C * B -  A / F * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G * B / D -  C * B / D -  A / F * B / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_345", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_345", "raw/question": "- C * G * x / A - B + D = F", "raw/answer": "x = - F / C / G * A -  B / C / G * A + D / C / G * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C * G * x / A + D = F + B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C * G * x / A = F + B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * G * x / A = - F -  B + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "G * x/A = - F / C -  B / C + D / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/A = - F / C / G -  B / C / G + D / C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F / C / G * A -  B / C / G * A + D / C / G * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_346", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_346", "raw/question": "- D = B + A - x + G - C / F", "raw/answer": "x = D + B + A + G -  C / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + A - x + G - C / F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A - x + G - C / F = - D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x + G - C / F = - D - B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - C / F = - D - B - A - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C / F to the right side", "equation": "- x = - D - B - A - G + C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = D + B + A + G -  C / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_347", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_347", "raw/question": "F + B + G - x - D - A = C", "raw/answer": "x = - C + F + B + G -  D -  A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "B + G - x - D - A = C - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G - x - D - A = C - F - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - A = C - F - B - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - A = C - F - B - G + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x = C - F - B - G + D + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - C + F + B + G -  D -  A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_348", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_348", "raw/question": "- G + F - A - C * D - B - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G + F -  A -  C * D -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "F - A - C * D - B - x = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A - C * D - B - x = G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C * D - B - x = G - F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C * D to the right side", "equation": "- B - x = G - F + A + C * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = G - F + A + C * D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G + F -  A -  C * D -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_349", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_349", "raw/question": "C = G * A + F + D - x + B", "raw/answer": "x = - C + G * A + F + D + B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G * A + F + D - x + B = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G * A to the right side", "equation": "F + D - x + B = C - G * A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D - x + B = C - G * A - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x + B = C - G * A - F - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x = C - G * A - F - D - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - C + G * A + F + D + B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_350", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_350", "raw/question": "- D - B - G * x + C + A - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / G -  B / G + C / G + A / G -  F / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B - G * x + C + A - F = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + C + A - F = D + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + A - F = D + B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x - F = D + B - C - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x = D + B - C - A + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x = -  D -  B + C + A -  F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / G -  B / G + C / G + A / G -  F / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_351", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_351", "raw/question": "D * G - x * A / B / F * C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D * G * F * B / A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D * G to the right side", "equation": "- x * A / B / F * C = - D * G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A / B / F * C = D * G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * A/B * C = D * G * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * A * C = D * G * F * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * C = D * G * F * B / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = D * G * F * B / A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_352", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_352", "raw/question": "G = C - x / A - B - F - D", "raw/answer": "x = - G * A + C * A -  B * A -  F * A -  D * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - x / A - B - F - D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - B - F - D = G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - F - D = G - C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - D = G - C + B + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / A = G - C + B + F + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A = - G + C -  B -  F -  D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - G * A + C * A -  B * A -  F * A -  D * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_353", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_353", "raw/question": "F = D + B + G - A - x / C", "raw/answer": "x = - F * C + D * C + B * C + G * C -  A * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + B + G - A - x / C = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B + G - A - x / C = F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G - A - x / C = F - D - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- A - x / C = F - D - B - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / C = F - D - B - G + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C = - F + D + B + G -  A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * C + D * C + B * C + G * C -  A * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_354", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_354", "raw/question": "D * B = A - C - F / x * G", "raw/answer": "x = F / (- D * B / G + A / G -  C / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - C - F / x * G = D * B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - F / x * G = D * B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x * G = D * B - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x * G = - D * B + A -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "F/x = - D * B / G + A / G -  C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (- D * B / G + A / G -  C / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_355", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_355", "raw/question": "F = A * B - x + C - D - G", "raw/answer": "x = - F + A * B + C -  D -  G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A * B - x + C - D - G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A * B to the right side", "equation": "- x + C - D - G = F - A * B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - G = F - A * B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - G = F - A * B - C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x = F - A * B - C + D + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - F + A * B + C -  D -  G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_356", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_356", "raw/question": "- B = A - G - x / D + C / F", "raw/answer": "x = B * D + A * D -  G * D + C / F * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - G - x / D + C / F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G - x / D + C / F = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + C / F = - B - A + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C / F to the right side", "equation": "- x / D = - B - A + G - C / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D = B + A -  G + C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = B * D + A * D -  G * D + C / F * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_357", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_357", "raw/question": "- B - C / F / A * D / x + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (-  B * A * F / C + G * A * F / C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C / F / A * D / x + G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C / F / A * D / x = B - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / F / A * D / x = -  B + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C/F * D/x = -  B * A + G * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "C * D/x = -  B * A * F + G * A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "D/x = -  B * A * F / C + G * A * F / C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (-  B * A * F / C + G * A * F / C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_358", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_358", "raw/question": "- C * x + A * G + F - D + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A * G / C + F / C -  D / C + B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A * G to the right side", "equation": "- C * x + F - D + B = - A * G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- C * x - D + B = - A * G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- C * x + B = - A * G - F + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C * x = - A * G - F + D - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x = A * G + F -  D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = A * G / C + F / C -  D / C + B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_359", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_359", "raw/question": "B + F - D * C / x + G + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (B / D + F / D + G / D + A / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "F - D * C / x + G + A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D * C / x + G + A = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D * C / x + A = - B - F - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D * C / x = - B - F - G - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * C / x = B + F + G + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "C/x = B / D + F / D + G / D + A / D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (B / D + F / D + G / D + A / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_360", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_360", "raw/question": "- x + F + D - C - G - A = B", "raw/answer": "x = - B + F + D -  C -  G -  A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x + D - C - G - A = B - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x - C - G - A = B - F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - G - A = B - F - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x - A = B - F - D + C + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x = B - F - D + C + G + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - B + F + D -  C -  G -  A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_361", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_361", "raw/question": "- A + B - C * x * F * G * D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  A / C / F / G / D + B / C / F / G / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "B - C * x * F * G * D = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C * x * F * G * D = A - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x * F * G * D = -  A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * F * G * D = -  A / C + B / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * G * D = -  A / C / F + B / C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * D = -  A / C / F / G + B / C / F / G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  A / C / F / G / D + B / C / F / G / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_362", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_362", "raw/question": "- B = A - F / x - G - D + C", "raw/answer": "x = F / (B + A -  G -  D + C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - F / x - G - D + C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x - G - D + C = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- F / x - D + C = - B - A + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x + C = - B - A + G + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x = - B - A + G + D - C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x = B + A -  G -  D + C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (B + A -  G -  D + C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_363", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_363", "raw/question": "- B = C - F * G / x - D - A", "raw/answer": "x = G / (B / F + C / F -  D / F -  A / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - F * G / x - D - A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F * G / x - D - A = - B - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * G / x - A = - B - C + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- F * G / x = - B - C + D + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * G / x = B + C -  D -  A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "G/x = B / F + C / F -  D / F -  A / F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (B / F + C / F -  D / F -  A / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_364", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_364", "raw/question": "- C - F - A / B - G - D - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C -  F -  A / B -  G -  D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F - A / B - G - D - x = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- A / B - G - D - x = C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A / B to the right side", "equation": "- G - D - x = C + F + A / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- D - x = C + F + A / B + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x = C + F + A / B + G + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C -  F -  A / B -  G -  D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_365", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_365", "raw/question": "- B = F - G + C - D * x * A", "raw/answer": "x = B / D / A + F / D / A -  G / D / A + C / D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - G + C - D * x * A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- G + C - D * x * A = - B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "C - D * x * A = - B - F + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- D * x * A = - B - F + G - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * x * A = B + F -  G + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A = B / D + F / D -  G / D + C / D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = B / D / A + F / D / A -  G / D / A + C / D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_366", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_366", "raw/question": "B + C / A / x - G - D - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / (- B * A + G * A + D * A + F * A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "C / A / x - G - D - F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "C / A / x - D - F = - B + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "C / A / x - F = - B + G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "C / A / x = - B + G + D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C/ x = - B * A + G * A + D * A + F * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (- B * A + G * A + D * A + F * A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_367", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_367", "raw/question": "G = F - B * x - C + A - D", "raw/answer": "x = - G / B + F / B -  C / B + A / B -  D / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - B * x - C + A - D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B * x - C + A - D = G - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B * x + A - D = G - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B * x - D = G - F + C - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B * x = G - F + C - A + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x = - G + F -  C + A -  D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = - G / B + F / B -  C / B + A / B -  D / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_368", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_368", "raw/question": "- C + D + A - G - F - x / B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C * B + D * B + A * B -  G * B -  F * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "D + A - G - F - x / B = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "A - G - F - x / B = C - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G - F - x / B = C - D - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- F - x / B = C - D - A + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / B = C - D - A + G + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B = -  C + D + A -  G -  F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C * B + D * B + A * B -  G * B -  F * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_369", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_369", "raw/question": "- D = x / G / C / A / F / B", "raw/answer": "x = - D * B * F * A * C * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x / G / C / A / F / B = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/G/C/A/F = - D * B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/G/C/A = - D * B * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/G/C = - D * B * F * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x/G = - D * B * F * A * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = - D * B * F * A * C * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_370", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_370", "raw/question": "- D - x + C / F - A + G - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D + C / F -  A + G -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x + C / F - A + G - B = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C / F to the right side", "equation": "- x - A + G - B = D - C / F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x + G - B = D - C / F + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = D - C / F + A - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = D - C / F + A - G + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D + C / F -  A + G -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_371", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_371", "raw/question": "F = D - x / A - C + B - G", "raw/answer": "x = - F * A + D * A -  C * A + B * A -  G * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - x / A - C + B - G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - C + B - G = F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / A + B - G = F - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - G = F - D + C - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / A = F - D + C - B + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A = - F + D -  C + B -  G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * A + D * A -  C * A + B * A -  G * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_372", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_372", "raw/question": "- G * x / B / D - C - F = A", "raw/answer": "x = - A / G * D * B -  C / G * D * B -  F / G * D * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / B / D - F = A + C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / B / D = A + C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x / B / D = - A -  C -  F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/B/D = - A / G -  C / G -  F / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/B = - A / G * D -  C / G * D -  F / G * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = - A / G * D * B -  C / G * D * B -  F / G * D * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_373", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_373", "raw/question": "F = G / A + B - C * D / x", "raw/answer": "x = D / (- F / C + G / A / C + B / C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G / A + B - C * D / x = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G / A to the right side", "equation": "B - C * D / x = F - G / A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C * D / x = F - G / A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * D / x = - F + G / A + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "D/x = - F / C + G / A / C + B / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (- F / C + G / A / C + B / C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_374", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_374", "raw/question": "- C = D + B * x / G * F / A", "raw/answer": "x = - C / B * A / F * G - D / B * A / F * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + B * x / G * F / A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B * x / G * F / A = - C - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/G * F/A = - C / B - D / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/G * F = - C / B * A - D / B * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/G = - C / B * A / F - D / B * A / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / B * A / F * G - D / B * A / F * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_375", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_375", "raw/question": "- x * C - G + D + B - F + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G / C + D / C + B / C -  F / C + A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x * C + D + B - F + A = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x * C + B - F + A = G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * C - F + A = G - D - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x * C + A = G - D - B + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * C = G - D - B + F - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * C = -  G + D + B -  F + A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G / C + D / C + B / C -  F / C + A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_376", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_376", "raw/question": "- D = A - C - B * x / G * F", "raw/answer": "x = D / B / F * G + A / B / F * G -  C / B / F * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - C - B * x / G * F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - B * x / G * F = - D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- B * x / G * F = - D - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x / G * F = D + A -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/G * F = D / B + A / B -  C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/G = D / B / F + A / B / F -  C / B / F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = D / B / F * G + A / B / F * G -  C / B / F * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_377", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_377", "raw/question": "- B = D - x / C * A * G - F", "raw/answer": "x = B / A / G * C + D / A / G * C -  F / A / G * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - x / C * A * G - F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / C * A * G - F = - B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / C * A * G = - B - D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C * A * G = B + D -  F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/C * G = B / A + D / A -  F / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/C = B / A / G + D / A / G -  F / A / G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / A / G * C + D / A / G * C -  F / A / G * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_378", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_378", "raw/question": "- F + G * D / C / x * B * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (F / G / B / A * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "G * D / C / x * B * A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "D/C/x * B * A = F / G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "D/C/x * A = F / G / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "D/C/x = F / G / B / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "D/ x = F / G / B / A * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (F / G / B / A * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_379", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_379", "raw/question": "G * A * x / F * D * B + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - C / G / A / D / B * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G * A * x / F * D * B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "A * x/F * D * B = - C / G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/F * D * B = - C / G / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/F * B = - C / G / A / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/F = - C / G / A / D / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / G / A / D / B * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_380", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_380", "raw/question": "D = G - x + A / F + C - B", "raw/answer": "x = - D + G + A / F + C -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - x + A / F + C - B = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x + A / F + C - B = D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A / F to the right side", "equation": "- x + C - B = D - G - A / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = D - G - A / F - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = D - G - A / F - C + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - D + G + A / F + C -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_381", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_381", "raw/question": "- G / B / C * x + F / D - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / D * C * B / G -  A * C * B / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F / D to the right side", "equation": "- G / B / C * x - A = - F / D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- G / B / C * x = - F / D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / B / C * x = F / D -  A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "G/B * x = F / D * C -  A * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "G * x = F / D * C * B -  A * C * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = F / D * C * B / G -  A * C * B / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_382", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_382", "raw/question": "A / G + C + B - D / x * F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (A / G / F + C / F + B / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A / G to the right side", "equation": "C + B - D / x * F = - A / G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B - D / x * F = - A / G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D / x * F = - A / G - C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x * F = A / G + C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "D/x = A / G / F + C / F + B / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (A / G / F + C / F + B / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_383", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_383", "raw/question": "D - F * G / x - B - C / A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / (D / F -  B / F -  C / A / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F * G / x - B - C / A = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F * G / x - C / A = - D + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C / A to the right side", "equation": "- F * G / x = - D + B + C / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * G / x = D -  B -  C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "G/x = D / F -  B / F -  C / A / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (D / F -  B / F -  C / A / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_384", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_384", "raw/question": "- C - D + F + G + x * B - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / B + D / B - F / B - G / B + A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- D + F + G + x * B - A = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "F + G + x * B - A = C + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "G + x * B - A = C + D - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x * B - A = C + D - F - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x * B = C + D - F - G + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = C / B + D / B - F / B - G / B + A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_385", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_385", "raw/question": "A + G / B - F + C - x - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A + G / B -  F + C -  D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G / B - F + C - x - D = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G / B to the right side", "equation": "- F + C - x - D = - A - G / B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "C - x - D = - A - G / B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - D = - A - G / B + F - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - A - G / B + F - C + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = A + G / B -  F + C -  D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_386", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_386", "raw/question": "- A = F * B + C - G * D * x", "raw/answer": "x = A / G / D + F * B / G / D + C / G / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F * B + C - G * D * x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F * B to the right side", "equation": "C - G * D * x = - A - F * B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G * D * x = - A - F * B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * D * x = A + F * B + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "D * x = A / G + F * B / G + C / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = A / G / D + F * B / G / D + C / G / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_387", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_387", "raw/question": "- A / F = G - x - C - D - B", "raw/answer": "x = A / F + G -  C -  D -  B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - x - C - D - B = - A / F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - C - D - B = - A / F - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - B = - A / F - G + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - B = - A / F - G + C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x = - A / F - G + C + D + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = A / F + G -  C -  D -  B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_388", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_388", "raw/question": "B = x * C - A + G - D + F", "raw/answer": "x = B / C + A / C - G / C + D / C - F / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x * C - A + G - D + F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x * C + G - D + F = B + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x * C - D + F = B + A - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x * C + F = B + A - G + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x * C = B + A - G + D - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / C + A / C - G / C + D / C - F / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_389", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_389", "raw/question": "x * C * F * A + B - D + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - B / C / F / A + D / C / F / A - G / C / F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x * C * F * A - D + G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x * C * F * A + G = - B + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x * C * F * A = - B + D - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * F * A = - B / C + D / C - G / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - B / C / F + D / C / F - G / C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / C / F / A + D / C / F / A - G / C / F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_390", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_390", "raw/question": "- B + A - x * D - C + F + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / D + A / D -  C / D + F / D + G / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "A - x * D - C + F + G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * D - C + F + G = B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * D + F + G = B - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x * D + G = B - A + C - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x * D = B - A + C - F - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * D = -  B + A -  C + F + G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / D + A / D -  C / D + F / D + G / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_391", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_391", "raw/question": "- G / F * x * D * A / C - B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B * F / G / D * C / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G / F * x * D * A / C = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / F * x * D * A / C = -  B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "G * x * D * A/C = -  B * F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * D * A/C = -  B * F / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x * A/C = -  B * F / G / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  B * F / G / D * C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B * F / G / D * C / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_392", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_392", "raw/question": "C * D - B - x / A / F + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C * D * F * A -  B * F * A + G * F * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C * D to the right side", "equation": "- B - x / A / F + G = - C * D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A / F + G = - C * D + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x / A / F = - C * D + B - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A / F = C * D -  B + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/A = C * D * F -  B * F + G * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = C * D * F * A -  B * F * A + G * F * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_393", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_393", "raw/question": "- F = G / x * C * B * D + A", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- F / C / B / D - A / C / B / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G / x * C * B * D + A = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "G / x * C * B * D = - F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "G/x * B * D = - F / C - A / C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "G/x * D = - F / C / B - A / C / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "G/x = - F / C / B / D - A / C / B / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- F / C / B / D - A / C / B / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_394", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_394", "raw/question": "- C * D = B - A / x / G - F", "raw/answer": "x = A / (C * D * G + B * G -  F * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - A / x / G - F = - C * D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A / x / G - F = - C * D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- A / x / G = - C * D - B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / x / G = C * D + B -  F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "A/x = C * D * G + B * G -  F * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (C * D * G + B * G -  F * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_395", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_395", "raw/question": "C - A / G - F - x * B - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C / B -  A / G / B -  F / B -  D / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A / G - F - x * B - D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A / G to the right side", "equation": "- F - x * B - D = - C + A / G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x * B - D = - C + A / G + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * B = - C + A / G + F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B = C -  A / G -  F -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = C / B -  A / G / B -  F / B -  D / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_396", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_396", "raw/question": "- C - F - D / B - A - G / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / (-  C -  F -  D / B -  A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F - D / B - A - G / x = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D / B - A - G / x = C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D / B to the right side", "equation": "- A - G / x = C + F + D / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- G / x = C + F + D / B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / x = -  C -  F -  D / B -  A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (-  C -  F -  D / B -  A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_397", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_397", "raw/question": "- A + F / D * x * B * C - G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A * D / F / B / C + G * D / F / B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "F / D * x * B * C - G = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "F / D * x * B * C = A + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "F * x * B * C = A * D + G * D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * B * C = A * D / F + G * D / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x * C = A * D / F / B + G * D / F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = A * D / F / B / C + G * D / F / B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_398", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_398", "raw/question": "- F = G - C * x / D / B + A", "raw/answer": "x = F / C * B * D + G / C * B * D + A / C * B * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - C * x / D / B + A = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C * x / D / B + A = - F - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C * x / D / B = - F - G - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x / D / B = F + G + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/D/B = F / C + G / C + A / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/D = F / C * B + G / C * B + A / C * B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = F / C * B * D + G / C * B * D + A / C * B * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_399", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_399", "raw/question": "- C - F + B - G - x / D / A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C * A * D -  F * A * D + B * A * D -  G * A * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F + B - G - x / D / A = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "B - G - x / D / A = C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G - x / D / A = C + F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / D / A = C + F - B + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D / A = -  C -  F + B -  G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/D = -  C * A -  F * A + B * A -  G * A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C * A * D -  F * A * D + B * A * D -  G * A * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_400", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_400", "raw/question": "- G = D * B + A - C / x / F", "raw/answer": "x = C / (G * F + D * B * F + A * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D * B + A - C / x / F = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D * B to the right side", "equation": "A - C / x / F = - G - D * B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C / x / F = - G - D * B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x / F = G + D * B + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "C/x = G * F + D * B * F + A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (G * F + D * B * F + A * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_401", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_401", "raw/question": "- F = D + B + A - C / x / G", "raw/answer": "x = C / (F * G + D * G + B * G + A * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + B + A - C / x / G = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B + A - C / x / G = - F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A - C / x / G = - F - D - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C / x / G = - F - D - B - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / x / G = F + D + B + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "C/x = F * G + D * G + B * G + A * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (F * G + D * G + B * G + A * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_402", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_402", "raw/question": "- B = A * G - D - F * C * x", "raw/answer": "x = B / F / C + A * G / F / C -  D / F / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A * G - D - F * C * x = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A * G to the right side", "equation": "- D - F * C * x = - B - A * G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * C * x = - B - A * G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * C * x = B + A * G -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "C * x = B / F + A * G / F -  D / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / F / C + A * G / F / C -  D / F / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_403", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_403", "raw/question": "- F * D * G * x * B / A = C", "raw/answer": "x = - C / F / D / G * A / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * D * G * x * B / A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "D * G * x * B/A = - C / F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "G * x * B/A = - C / F / D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * B/A = - C / F / D / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x * B = - C / F / D / G * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / F / D / G * A / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_404", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_404", "raw/question": "- A * G / x - B + F - C - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / (-  B / A + F / A -  C / A -  D / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A * G / x + F - C - D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A * G / x - C - D = B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- A * G / x - D = B - F + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- A * G / x = B - F + C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * G / x = -  B + F -  C -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "G/x = -  B / A + F / A -  C / A -  D / A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (-  B / A + F / A -  C / A -  D / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_405", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_405", "raw/question": "- A = D + B * G / C / x - F", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- A / B * C - D / B * C + F / B * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + B * G / C / x - F = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B * G / C / x - F = - A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "B * G / C / x = - A - D + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "G/C/x = - A / B - D / B + F / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "G/ x = - A / B * C - D / B * C + F / B * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- A / B * C - D / B * C + F / B * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_406", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_406", "raw/question": "A + D - F / G - x / B * C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / C * B + D / C * B -  F / G / C * B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D - F / G - x / B * C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / G - x / B * C = - A - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F / G to the right side", "equation": "- x / B * C = - A - D + F / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / B * C = A + D -  F / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/B = A / C + D / C -  F / G / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x = A / C * B + D / C * B -  F / G / C * B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_407", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_407", "raw/question": "- B = D - F / G - x / A - C", "raw/answer": "x = B * A + D * A -  F / G * A -  C * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - F / G - x / A - C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F / G - x / A - C = - B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F / G to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - C = - B - D + F / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / A = - B - D + F / G + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A = B + D -  F / G -  C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = B * A + D * A -  F / G * A -  C * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_408", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_408", "raw/question": "- C + D + G - A * F - B * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C / B + D / B + G / B -  A * F / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "D + G - A * F - B * x = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "G - A * F - B * x = C - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- A * F - B * x = C - D - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - A * F to the right side", "equation": "- B * x = C - D - G + A * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * x = -  C + D + G -  A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C / B + D / B + G / B -  A * F / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_409", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_409", "raw/question": "C - A = G - x - D - F + B", "raw/answer": "x = - C + A + G -  D -  F + B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - x - D - F + B = C - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x - D - F + B = C - A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x - F + B = C - A - G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x + B = C - A - G + D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x = C - A - G + D + F - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - C + A + G -  D -  F + B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_410", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_410", "raw/question": "- C = F * G * x / D / A * B", "raw/answer": "x = - C / F / G / B * A * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F * G * x / D / A * B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "G * x/D/A * B = - C / F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/D/A * B = - C / F / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/D/A = - C / F / G / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/D = - C / F / G / B * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / F / G / B * A * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_411", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_411", "raw/question": "A = G - D + B * F / x + C", "raw/answer": "x = F / (A / B - G / B + D / B - C / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - D + B * F / x + C = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D + B * F / x + C = A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "B * F / x + C = A - G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B * F / x = A - G + D - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "F/x = A / B - G / B + D / B - C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (A / B - G / B + D / B - C / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_412", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_412", "raw/question": "A = G + F + D + C / x + B", "raw/answer": "x = C / (A - G - F - D - B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + F + D + C / x + B = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "F + D + C / x + B = A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D + C / x + B = A - G - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "C / x + B = A - G - F - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "C / x = A - G - F - D - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (A - G - F - D - B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_413", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_413", "raw/question": "- B + D - A - x / C + G = F", "raw/answer": "x = - F * C -  B * C + D * C -  A * C + G * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "D - A - x / C + G = F + B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A - x / C + G = F + B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- x / C + G = F + B - D + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x / C = F + B - D + A - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C = - F -  B + D -  A + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * C -  B * C + D * C -  A * C + G * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_414", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_414", "raw/question": "- F - x / G + C - B / A + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  F * G + C * G -  B / A * G + D * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x / G + C - B / A + D = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / G - B / A + D = F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B / A to the right side", "equation": "- x / G + D = F - C + B / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / G = F - C + B / A - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G = -  F + C -  B / A + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = -  F * G + C * G -  B / A * G + D * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_415", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_415", "raw/question": "- B - G - x / D + A + C + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B * D -  G * D + A * D + C * D + F * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G - x / D + A + C + F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + A + C + F = B + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + C + F = B + G - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + F = B + G - A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / D = B + G - A - C - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D = -  B -  G + A + C + F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B * D -  G * D + A * D + C * D + F * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_416", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_416", "raw/question": "- B + G = A - x / C + F - D", "raw/answer": "x = B * C - G * C + A * C + F * C -  D * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - x / C + F - D = - B + G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / C + F - D = - B + G - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / C - D = - B + G - A - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x / C = - B + G - A - F + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C = B - G + A + F -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = B * C - G * C + A * C + F * C -  D * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_417", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_417", "raw/question": "- F * D * x - B + G + C / A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B / F / D + G / F / D + C / A / F / D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F * D * x + G + C / A = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- F * D * x + C / A = B - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C / A to the right side", "equation": "- F * D * x = B - G - C / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * D * x = -  B + G + C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "D * x = -  B / F + G / F + C / A / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B / F / D + G / F / D + C / A / F / D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_418", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_418", "raw/question": "B = F / x / C / G / A / D", "raw/answer": "x = F / (B * D * A * G * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F / x / C / G / A / D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "F/x/C/G/A = B * D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "F/x/C/G = B * D * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "F/x/C = B * D * A * G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "F/x = B * D * A * G * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (B * D * A * G * C)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_419", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_419", "raw/question": "- D = G - C + A * x * F / B", "raw/answer": "x = - D / A * B / F - G / A * B / F + C / A * B / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - C + A * x * F / B = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C + A * x * F / B = - D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A * x * F / B = - D - G + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * F/B = - D / A - G / A + C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * F = - D / A * B - G / A * B + C / A * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / A * B / F - G / A * B / F + C / A * B / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_420", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_420", "raw/question": "D = G + C - B - F * A / x", "raw/answer": "x = A / (- D / F + G / F + C / F -  B / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + C - B - F * A / x = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C - B - F * A / x = D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- B - F * A / x = D - G - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F * A / x = D - G - C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * A / x = - D + G + C -  B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "A/x = - D / F + G / F + C / F -  B / F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (- D / F + G / F + C / F -  B / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_421", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_421", "raw/question": "F + C = G - B - x / A + D", "raw/answer": "x = - F * A - C * A + G * A -  B * A + D * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - B - x / A + D = F + C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- B - x / A + D = F + C - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A + D = F + C - G + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x / A = F + C - G + B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A = - F - C + G -  B + D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * A - C * A + G * A -  B * A + D * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_422", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_422", "raw/question": "- G * x * A / B / C - D = F", "raw/answer": "x = - F / G * C * B / A -  D / G * C * B / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- G * x * A / B / C = F + D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x * A / B / C = - F -  D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * A/B/C = - F / G -  D / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x * A/B = - F / G * C -  D / G * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - F / G * C * B -  D / G * C * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F / G * C * B / A -  D / G * C * B / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_423", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_423", "raw/question": "D + F * B + A + C - G - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D + F * B + A + C -  G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F * B + A + C - G - x = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F * B to the right side", "equation": "A + C - G - x = - D - F * B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C - G - x = - D - F * B - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G - x = - D - F * B - A - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - D - F * B - A - C + G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = D + F * B + A + C -  G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_424", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_424", "raw/question": "F = D - C - G + x - B + A", "raw/answer": "x = F - D + C + G + B - A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - C - G + x - B + A = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - G + x - B + A = F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- G + x - B + A = F - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x - B + A = F - D + C + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "x + A = F - D + C + G + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = F - D + C + G + B - A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_425", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_425", "raw/question": "- G = D - C - x * A + F * B", "raw/answer": "x = G / A + D / A -  C / A + F * B / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - C - x * A + F * B = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - x * A + F * B = - G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A + F * B = - G - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F * B to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = - G - D + C - F * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = G + D -  C + F * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = G / A + D / A -  C / A + F * B / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_426", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_426", "raw/question": "- G - x / F / A + C + B / D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G * A * F + C * A * F + B / D * A * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / A + C + B / D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / A + B / D = G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B / D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / A = G - C - B / D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F / A = -  G + C + B / D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/F = -  G * A + C * A + B / D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G * A * F + C * A * F + B / D * A * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_427", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_427", "raw/question": "- F + D = G - x / C * A + B", "raw/answer": "x = F / A * C - D / A * C + G / A * C + B / A * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G - x / C * A + B = - F + D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x / C * A + B = - F + D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / C * A = - F + D - G - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C * A = F - D + G + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/C = F / A - D / A + G / A + B / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = F / A * C - D / A * C + G / A * C + B / A * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_428", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_428", "raw/question": "G = C - x * A - F * B - D", "raw/answer": "x = - G / A + C / A -  F * B / A -  D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - x * A - F * B - D = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A - F * B - D = G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F * B to the right side", "equation": "- x * A - D = G - C + F * B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * A = G - C + F * B + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - G + C -  F * B -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - G / A + C / A -  F * B / A -  D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_429", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_429", "raw/question": "- F = D - C - G + x + B + A", "raw/answer": "x = - F - D + C + G - B - A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - C - G + x + B + A = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C - G + x + B + A = - F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- G + x + B + A = - F - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x + B + A = - F - D + C + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x + A = - F - D + C + G - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F - D + C + G - B - A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_430", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_430", "raw/question": "C + G - x * A / D + F / B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = C * D / A + G * D / A + F / B * D / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G - x * A / D + F / B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x * A / D + F / B = - C - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F / B to the right side", "equation": "- x * A / D = - C - G - F / B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A / D = C + G + F / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x * A = C * D + G * D + F / B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = C * D / A + G * D / A + F / B * D / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_431", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_431", "raw/question": "- x / G / B / D * F * C + A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / F / C * D * B * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / G / B / D * F * C = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G / B / D * F * C = A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/G/B/D * C = A / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/G/B/D = A / F / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/G/B = A / F / C * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x/G = A / F / C * D * B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = A / F / C * D * B * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_432", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_432", "raw/question": "- A + B / F / x / C - G - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (A * C * F + G * C * F + D * C * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "B / F / x / C - G - D = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "B / F / x / C - D = A + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "B / F / x / C = A + G + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "B/F/x = A * C + G * C + D * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "B/ x = A * C * F + G * C * F + D * C * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (A * C * F + G * C * F + D * C * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_433", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_433", "raw/question": "- C = F - B / G / D * x / A", "raw/answer": "x = C * D * G / B * A + F * D * G / B * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - B / G / D * x / A = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B / G / D * x / A = - C - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / G / D * x / A = C + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "B/G * x/A = C * D + F * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "B * x/A = C * D * G + F * D * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/A = C * D * G / B + F * D * G / B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = C * D * G / B * A + F * D * G / B * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_434", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_434", "raw/question": "A + C - G * x / D + B + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / G * D + C / G * D + B / G * D + F / G * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "C - G * x / D + B + F = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / D + B + F = - A - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / D + F = - A - C - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / D = - A - C - B - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x / D = A + C + B + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/D = A / G + C / G + B / G + F / G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = A / G * D + C / G * D + B / G * D + F / G * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_435", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_435", "raw/question": "G = F / D + A + B - C * x", "raw/answer": "x = - G / C + F / D / C + A / C + B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F / D + A + B - C * x = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F / D to the right side", "equation": "A + B - C * x = G - F / D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "B - C * x = G - F / D - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C * x = G - F / D - A - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x = - G + F / D + A + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = - G / C + F / D / C + A / C + B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_436", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_436", "raw/question": "- F = A * C + G - B + D - x", "raw/answer": "x = F + A * C + G -  B + D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A * C + G - B + D - x = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A * C to the right side", "equation": "G - B + D - x = - F - A * C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- B + D - x = - F - A * C - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "D - x = - F - A * C - G + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - F - A * C - G + B - D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = F + A * C + G -  B + D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_437", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_437", "raw/question": "- x / C / D / F / G * B = A", "raw/answer": "x = - A / B * G * F * D * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / C / D / F / G * B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/C/D/F/G = - A / B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x/C/D/F = - A / B * G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/C/D = - A / B * G * F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/C = - A / B * G * F * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = - A / B * G * F * D * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_438", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_438", "raw/question": "F - B - C + x / D / G * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - F / A * G * D + B / A * G * D + C / A * G * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- B - C + x / D / G * A = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C + x / D / G * A = - F + B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x / D / G * A = - F + B + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/D/G = - F / A + B / A + C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x/D = - F / A * G + B / A * G + C / A * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = - F / A * G * D + B / A * G * D + C / A * G * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_439", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_439", "raw/question": "D + x * B - A - C + G - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - D / B + A / B + C / B - G / B + F / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x * B - A - C + G - F = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x * B - C + G - F = - D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x * B + G - F = - D + A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x * B - F = - D + A + C - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x * B = - D + A + C - G + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = - D / B + A / B + C / B - G / B + F / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_440", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_440", "raw/question": "- C / A + F - x / G / D + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C / A * D * G + F * D * G + B * D * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C / A to the right side", "equation": "F - x / G / D + B = C / A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / G / D + B = C / A - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / G / D = C / A - F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G / D = -  C / A + F + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/G = -  C / A * D + F * D + B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C / A * D * G + F * D * G + B * D * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_441", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_441", "raw/question": "- B = A - F / x / G + C - D", "raw/answer": "x = F / (B * G + A * G + C * G -  D * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - F / x / G + C - D = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / G + C - D = - B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / G - D = - B - A - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / G = - B - A - C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x / G = B + A + C -  D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "F/x = B * G + A * G + C * G -  D * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (B * G + A * G + C * G -  D * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_442", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_442", "raw/question": "- F * B * A * x * G - C - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  C / F / B / A / G -  D / F / B / A / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F * B * A * x * G - D = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F * B * A * x * G = C + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * B * A * x * G = -  C -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "B * A * x * G = -  C / F -  D / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "A * x * G = -  C / F / B -  D / F / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * G = -  C / F / B / A -  D / F / B / A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = -  C / F / B / A / G -  D / F / B / A / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_443", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_443", "raw/question": "- D - G - x / F / A * B - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / B * A * F -  G / B * A * F -  C / B * A * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- G - x / F / A * B - C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / A * B - C = D + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F / A * B = D + G + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F / A * B = -  D -  G -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/F/A = -  D / B -  G / B -  C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/F = -  D / B * A -  G / B * A -  C / B * A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / B * A * F -  G / B * A * F -  C / B * A * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_444", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_444", "raw/question": "- C = F * G - x / A / D - B", "raw/answer": "x = C * D * A + F * G * D * A -  B * D * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F * G - x / A / D - B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F * G to the right side", "equation": "- x / A / D - B = - C - F * G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A / D = - C - F * G + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A / D = C + F * G -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x/A = C * D + F * G * D -  B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = C * D * A + F * G * D * A -  B * D * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_445", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_445", "raw/question": "G - D * A / x - C * B + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (G / D -  C * B / D + F / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- D * A / x - C * B + F = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C * B to the right side", "equation": "- D * A / x + F = - G + C * B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- D * A / x = - G + C * B - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D * A / x = G -  C * B + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "A/x = G / D -  C * B / D + F / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (G / D -  C * B / D + F / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_446", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_446", "raw/question": "- D = B - F + x - G + A + C", "raw/answer": "x = - D - B + F + G - A - C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - F + x - G + A + C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F + x - G + A + C = - D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x - G + A + C = - D - B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x + A + C = - D - B + F + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x + C = - D - B + F + G - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = - D - B + F + G - A - C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_447", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_447", "raw/question": "- C = B / x * A - F + G - D", "raw/answer": "x = B / (- C / A + F / A - G / A + D / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B / x * A - F + G - D = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "B / x * A + G - D = - C + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "B / x * A - D = - C + F - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "B / x * A = - C + F - G + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "B/x = - C / A + F / A - G / A + D / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (- C / A + F / A - G / A + D / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_448", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_448", "raw/question": "F = C / D / x / B * A / G", "raw/answer": "x = C / (F * G / A * B * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C / D / x / B * A / G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "C/D/x/B * A = F * G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "C/D/x/B = F * G / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "C/D/x = F * G / A * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/ x = F * G / A * B * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x = C / (F * G / A * B * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_449", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_449", "raw/question": "- B = x / F * D / C / G / A", "raw/answer": "x = - B * A * G * C / D * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x / F * D / C / G / A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x/F * D/C/G = - B * A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x/F * D/C = - B * A * G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x/F * D = - B * A * G * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "x/F = - B * A * G * C / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * A * G * C / D * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_450", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_450", "raw/question": "B = C - D / A - x * G - F", "raw/answer": "x = - B / G + C / G -  D / A / G -  F / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - D / A - x * G - F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- D / A - x * G - F = B - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D / A to the right side", "equation": "- x * G - F = B - C + D / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x * G = B - C + D / A + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G = - B + C -  D / A -  F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / G + C / G -  D / A / G -  F / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_451", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_451", "raw/question": "x + B + D + G + C + A - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - B - D - G - C - A + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x + D + G + C + A - F = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x + G + C + A - F = - B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x + C + A - F = - B - D - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x + A - F = - B - D - G - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x - F = - B - D - G - C - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x = - B - D - G - C - A + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_452", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_452", "raw/question": "- A / x * G / D * F - C + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (-  C * D / G / F + B * D / G / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- A / x * G / D * F + B = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A / x * G / D * F = C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / x * G / D * F = -  C + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "A/x * G * F = -  C * D + B * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "A/x * F = -  C * D / G + B * D / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "A/x = -  C * D / G / F + B * D / G / F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (-  C * D / G / F + B * D / G / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_453", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_453", "raw/question": "F = A + D * C - x * B / G", "raw/answer": "x = - F * G / B + A * G / B + D * C * G / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A + D * C - x * B / G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D * C - x * B / G = F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D * C to the right side", "equation": "- x * B / G = F - A - D * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * B / G = - F + A + D * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x * B = - F * G + A * G + D * C * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * G / B + A * G / B + D * C * G / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_454", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_454", "raw/question": "- G + B - C / A / D * x = F", "raw/answer": "x = - F * D * A / C -  G * D * A / C + B * D * A / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "B - C / A / D * x = F + G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- C / A / D * x = F + G - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C / A / D * x = - F -  G + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "C/A * x = - F * D -  G * D + B * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "C * x = - F * D * A -  G * D * A + B * D * A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = - F * D * A / C -  G * D * A / C + B * D * A / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_455", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_455", "raw/question": "- D - A + G + x / F - C + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D * F + A * F - G * F + C * F - B * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- A + G + x / F - C + B = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "G + x / F - C + B = D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x / F - C + B = D + A - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x / F + B = D + A - G + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x / F = D + A - G + C - B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = D * F + A * F - G * F + C * F - B * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_456", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_456", "raw/question": "D + B - G - C * x * A = F", "raw/answer": "x = - F / C / A + D / C / A + B / C / A -  G / C / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B - G - C * x * A = F - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G - C * x * A = F - D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- C * x * A = F - D - B + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * x * A = - F + D + B -  G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - F / C + D / C + B / C -  G / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - F / C / A + D / C / A + B / C / A -  G / C / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_457", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_457", "raw/question": "B * C = A - G * x / D / F", "raw/answer": "x = - B * C / G * F * D + A / G * F * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - G * x / D / F = B * C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x / D / F = B * C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x / D / F = - B * C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/D/F = - B * C / G + A / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/D = - B * C / G * F + A / G * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * C / G * F * D + A / G * F * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_458", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_458", "raw/question": "- F = A - C - D / x * G - B", "raw/answer": "x = D / (F / G + A / G -  C / G -  B / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - C - D / x * G - B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- C - D / x * G - B = - F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- D / x * G - B = - F - A + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- D / x * G = - F - A + C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x * G = F + A -  C -  B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "D/x = F / G + A / G -  C / G -  B / G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (F / G + A / G -  C / G -  B / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_459", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_459", "raw/question": "D = C - A + x / G / F - B", "raw/answer": "x = D * F * G - C * F * G + A * F * G + B * F * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - A + x / G / F - B = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- A + x / G / F - B = D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x / G / F - B = D - C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "x / G / F = D - C + A + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/G = D * F - C * F + A * F + B * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = D * F * G - C * F * G + A * F * G + B * F * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_460", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_460", "raw/question": "- C * F / x * B + D + G - A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (D / C / B + G / C / B -  A / C / B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- C * F / x * B + G - A = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- C * F / x * B - A = - D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- C * F / x * B = - D - G + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * F / x * B = D + G -  A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "F/x * B = D / C + G / C -  A / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "F/x = D / C / B + G / C / B -  A / C / B"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (D / C / B + G / C / B -  A / C / B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_461", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_461", "raw/question": "D + F + B - x / A * G = C", "raw/answer": "x = - C / G * A + D / G * A + F / G * A + B / G * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "F + B - x / A * G = C - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "B - x / A * G = C - D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / A * G = C - D - F - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A * G = - C + D + F + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/A = - C / G + D / G + F / G + B / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / G * A + D / G * A + F / G * A + B / G * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_462", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_462", "raw/question": "- F + C / A - B - D / G / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D / (-  F * G + C / A * G -  B * G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "C / A - B - D / G / x = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C / A to the right side", "equation": "- B - D / G / x = F - C / A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- D / G / x = F - C / A + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / G / x = -  F + C / A -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "D/ x = -  F * G + C / A * G -  B * G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (-  F * G + C / A * G -  B * G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_463", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_463", "raw/question": "B = D + A - x - G + C - F", "raw/answer": "x = - B + D + A -  G + C -  F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + A - x - G + C - F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "A - x - G + C - F = B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x - G + C - F = B - D - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x + C - F = B - D - A + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x - F = B - D - A + G - C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x = B - D - A + G - C + F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = - B + D + A -  G + C -  F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_464", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_464", "raw/question": "- G + x * C * B + A - D + F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / C / B - A / C / B + D / C / B - F / C / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x * C * B + A - D + F = G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x * C * B - D + F = G - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x * C * B + F = G - A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x * C * B = G - A + D - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x * B = G / C - A / C + D / C - F / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = G / C / B - A / C / B + D / C / B - F / C / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_465", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_465", "raw/question": "- F + A + D + G * x * C + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / G / C - A / G / C - D / G / C - B / G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "A + D + G * x * C + B = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "D + G * x * C + B = F - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "G * x * C + B = F - A - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G * x * C = F - A - D - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * C = F / G - A / G - D / G - B / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = F / G / C - A / G / C - D / G / C - B / G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_466", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_466", "raw/question": "B - A - D - G - F + x / C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - B * C + A * C + D * C + G * C + F * C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A - D - G - F + x / C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D - G - F + x / C = - B + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- G - F + x / C = - B + A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- F + x / C = - B + A + D + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x / C = - B + A + D + G + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * C + A * C + D * C + G * C + F * C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_467", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_467", "raw/question": "- x + D - F + A * G + B - C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = D -  F + A * G + B -  C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x - F + A * G + B - C = - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- x + A * G + B - C = - D + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A * G to the right side", "equation": "- x + B - C = - D + F - A * G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x - C = - D + F - A * G - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x = - D + F - A * G - B + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = D -  F + A * G + B -  C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_468", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_468", "raw/question": "- A = G + C - F - B / D * x", "raw/answer": "x = A * D / B + G * D / B + C * D / B -  F * D / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + C - F - B / D * x = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C - F - B / D * x = - A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F - B / D * x = - A - G - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- B / D * x = - A - G - C + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / D * x = A + G + C -  F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "B * x = A * D + G * D + C * D -  F * D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = A * D / B + G * D / B + C * D / B -  F * D / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_469", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_469", "raw/question": "- F = D - A / C - G / B / x", "raw/answer": "x = G / (F * B + D * B -  A / C * B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - A / C - G / B / x = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A / C - G / B / x = - F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A / C to the right side", "equation": "- G / B / x = - F - D + A / C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / B / x = F + D -  A / C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "G/ x = F * B + D * B -  A / C * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (F * B + D * B -  A / C * B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_470", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u264b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_470", "raw/question": "C = D / B - F - G * x + A", "raw/answer": "x = - C / G + D / B / G -  F / G + A / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D / B - F - G * x + A = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D / B to the right side", "equation": "- F - G * x + A = C - D / B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- G * x + A = C - D / B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x = C - D / B + F - A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x = - C + D / B -  F + A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / G + D / B / G -  F / G + A / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_471", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_471", "raw/question": "- B - F - D + C - x * A / G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  B * G / A -  F * G / A -  D * G / A + C * G / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- F - D + C - x * A / G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "- D + C - x * A / G = B + F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "C - x * A / G = B + F + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * A / G = B + F + D - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * A / G = -  B -  F -  D + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x * A = -  B * G -  F * G -  D * G + C * G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = -  B * G / A -  F * G / A -  D * G / A + C * G / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_472", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_472", "raw/question": "- F = A / G + C + B - D / x", "raw/answer": "x = D / (F + A / G + C + B)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A / G + C + B - D / x = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A / G to the right side", "equation": "C + B - D / x = - F - A / G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "B - D / x = - F - A / G - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- D / x = - F - A / G - C - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "D / x = F + A / G + C + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (F + A / G + C + B)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_473", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_473", "raw/question": "- B = G + C + x * A / F - D", "raw/answer": "x = - B * F / A - G * F / A - C * F / A + D * F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + C + x * A / F - D = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C + x * A / F - D = - B - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x * A / F - D = - B - G - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "x * A / F = - B - G - C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - B * F - G * F - C * F + D * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * F / A - G * F / A - C * F / A + D * F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_474", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_474", "raw/question": "G * A / F / x / D + C + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A / (- C / G * D * F - B / G * D * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G * A / F / x / D + B = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G * A / F / x / D = - C - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "A/F/x/D = - C / G - B / G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "A/F/x = - C / G * D - B / G * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "A/ x = - C / G * D * F - B / G * D * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "x = A / (- C / G * D * F - B / G * D * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_475", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_475", "raw/question": "B - A + C + G + F + D - x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B -  A + C + G + F + D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A + C + G + F + D - x = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "C + G + F + D - x = - B + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G + F + D - x = - B + A - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "F + D - x = - B + A - C - G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "D - x = - B + A - C - G - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- x = - B + A - C - G - F - D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = B -  A + C + G + F + D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_476", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_476", "raw/question": "- A - D - G / x / F - C = B", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- B * F -  A * F -  D * F -  C * F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D - G / x / F - C = B + A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- G / x / F - C = B + A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- G / x / F = B + A + D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G / x / F = - B -  A -  D -  C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "G/x = - B * F -  A * F -  D * F -  C * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- B * F -  A * F -  D * F -  C * F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_477", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_477", "raw/question": "F = D - A - B - C - x * G", "raw/answer": "x = - F / G + D / G -  A / G -  B / G -  C / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - A - B - C - x * G = F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A - B - C - x * G = F - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- B - C - x * G = F - D + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- C - x * G = F - D + A + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- x * G = F - D + A + B + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * G = - F + D -  A -  B -  C"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - F / G + D / G -  A / G -  B / G -  C / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_478", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_478", "raw/question": "B = G / C - F * x * A + D", "raw/answer": "x = - B / F / A + G / C / F / A + D / F / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G / C - F * x * A + D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G / C to the right side", "equation": "- F * x * A + D = B - G / C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F * x * A = B - G / C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F * x * A = - B + G / C + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x * A = - B / F + G / C / F + D / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / F / A + G / C / F / A + D / F / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_479", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_479", "raw/question": "- C = A - D - F / B * x / G", "raw/answer": "x = C * B / F * G + A * B / F * G -  D * B / F * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - D - F / B * x / G = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D - F / B * x / G = - C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- F / B * x / G = - C - A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / B * x / G = C + A -  D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "F * x/G = C * B + A * B -  D * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x/G = C * B / F + A * B / F -  D * B / F"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = C * B / F * G + A * B / F * G -  D * B / F * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_480", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_480", "raw/question": "B + C * A * F * D * G / x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / (- B / C / A / F / D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "C * A * F * D * G / x = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "A * F * D * G/x = - B / C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "F * D * G/x = - B / C / A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "D * G/x = - B / C / A / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * D to the right side", "equation": "G/x = - B / C / A / F / D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (- B / C / A / F / D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_481", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u266a \u264f \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_481", "raw/question": "F / C = A - B * D / x * G", "raw/answer": "x = D / (- F / C / B / G + A / B / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - B * D / x * G = F / C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B * D / x * G = F / C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B * D / x * G = - F / C + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "D/x * G = - F / C / B + A / B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "D/x = - F / C / B / G + A / B / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (- F / C / B / G + A / B / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_482", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_482", "raw/question": "G * D = F + A - x * C / B", "raw/answer": "x = - G * D * B / C + F * B / C + A * B / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F + A - x * C / B = G * D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "A - x * C / B = G * D - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x * C / B = G * D - F - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * C / B = - G * D + F + A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "x * C = - G * D * B + F * B + A * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = - G * D * B / C + F * B / C + A * B / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_483", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u269b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_483", "raw/question": "- A / C / D * x / F * G + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B * D * C / A / G * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- A / C / D * x / F * G = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / C / D * x / F * G = B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "A/C * x/F * G = B * D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "A * x/F * G = B * D * C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/F * G = B * D * C / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/F = B * D * C / A / G"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = B * D * C / A / G * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_484", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u269b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_484", "raw/question": "- D - A + F / x * G / B + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (D * B / G + A * B / G - C * B / G)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- A + F / x * G / B + C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "F / x * G / B + C = D + A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "F / x * G / B = D + A - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "F/x * G = D * B + A * B - C * B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "F/x = D * B / G + A * B / G - C * B / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (D * B / G + A * B / G - C * B / G)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_485", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u273e \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_485", "raw/question": "B = F - x / A + C - G * D", "raw/answer": "x = - B * A + F * A + C * A -  G * D * A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "F - x / A + C - G * D = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / A + C - G * D = B - F"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / A - G * D = B - F - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G * D to the right side", "equation": "- x / A = B - F - C + G * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / A = - B + F + C -  G * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * A + F * A + C * A -  G * D * A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_486", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_486", "raw/question": "- B - G - A - D + C - F + x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B + G + A + D - C + F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- G - A - D + C - F + x = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- A - D + C - F + x = B + G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "- D + C - F + x = B + G + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "C - F + x = B + G + A + D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- F + x = B + G + A + D - C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "x = B + G + A + D - C + F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_487", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u269b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_487", "raw/question": "C / B = A - F / D * G * x", "raw/answer": "x = - C / B * D / F / G + A * D / F / G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A - F / D * G * x = C / B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- F / D * G * x = C / B - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / D * G * x = - C / B + A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "F * G * x = - C / B * D + A * D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "G * x = - C / B * D / F + A * D / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x = - C / B * D / F / G + A * D / F / G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_488", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_488", "raw/question": "F + C - x / D + G * A + B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F * D + C * D + G * A * D + B * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "C - x / D + G * A + B = - F"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + G * A + B = - F - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G * A to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + B = - F - C - G * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x / D = - F - C - G * A - B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D = F + C + G * A + B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = F * D + C * D + G * A * D + B * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_489", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2194 \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2740 \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_489", "raw/question": "- B = x + D - G + F - C - A", "raw/answer": "x = - B - D + G - F + C + A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "x + D - G + F - C - A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x - G + F - C - A = - B - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "x + F - C - A = - B - D + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x - C - A = - B - D + G - F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "x - A = - B - D + G - F + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "x = - B - D + G - F + C + A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_490", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_490", "raw/question": "- A / C * F / D / x / B + G = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (G * C / A * B * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- A / C * F / D / x / B = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A / C * F / D / x / B = G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "A * F/D/x/B = G * C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "F/D/x/B = G * C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / B to the right side", "equation": "F/D/x = G * C / A * B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "F/ x = G * C / A * B * D"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (G * C / A * B * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_491", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_491", "raw/question": "- G * D - x / F * B + A + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  G * D / B * F + A / B * F + C / B * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - G * D to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * B + A + C = G * D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * B + C = G * D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / F * B = G * D - A - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / F * B = -  G * D + A + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/F = -  G * D / B + A / B + C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = -  G * D / B * F + A / B * F + C / B * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_492", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_492", "raw/question": "D - A * C * x / F + G = B", "raw/answer": "x = - B / A / C * F + D / A / C * F + G / A / C * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- A * C * x / F + G = B - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- A * C * x / F = B - D - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * C * x / F = - B + D + G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "C * x/F = - B / A + D / A + G / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x/F = - B / A / C + D / A / C + G / A / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / A / C * F + D / A / C * F + G / A / C * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_493", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u273e \u2659 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_493", "raw/question": "A - D + G + C + x / F * B = 0", "raw/answer": "x = - A / B * F + D / B * F - G / B * F - C / B * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- D + G + C + x / F * B = - A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "G + C + x / F * B = - A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C + x / F * B = - A + D - G"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "x / F * B = - A + D - G - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x/F = - A / B + D / B - G / B - C / B"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = - A / B * F + D / B * F - G / B * F - C / B * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_494", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2740 \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_494", "raw/question": "- A + G + C - B + x + F + D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = A - G - C + B - F - D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - A to the right side", "equation": "G + C - B + x + F + D = A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "C - B + x + F + D = A - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- B + x + F + D = A - G - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "x + F + D = A - G - C + B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x + D = A - G - C + B - F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = A - G - C + B - F - D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_495", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u273e \u263a \u273e \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_495", "raw/question": "B + D = C - x / G / F * A", "raw/answer": "x = - B / A * F * G - D / A * F * G + C / A * F * G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C - x / G / F * A = B + D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x / G / F * A = B + D - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / G / F * A = - B - D + C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x/G/F = - B / A - D / A + C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x/G = - B / A * F - D / A * F + C / A * F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / G to the right side", "equation": "x = - B / A * F * G - D / A * F * G + C / A * F * G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_496", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 \u266a \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u263a \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u264b \u273e \u269b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_496", "raw/question": "B / G - C - F / x / D / A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = F / (B / G * A * D -  C * A * D)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B / G to the right side", "equation": "- C - F / x / D / A = - B / G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "- F / x / D / A = - B / G + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "F / x / D / A = B / G -  C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move / A to the right side", "equation": "F/x/D = B / G * A -  C * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "F/x = B / G * A * D -  C * A * D"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "x = F / (B / G * A * D -  C * A * D)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_497", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u264f \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264f"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_497", "raw/question": "- G * x * C + B - D - F * A = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / G / C -  D / G / C -  F * A / G / C", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- G * x * C - D - F * A = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- G * x * C - F * A = - B + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F * A to the right side", "equation": "- G * x * C = - B + D + F * A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "G * x * C = B -  D -  F * A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x * C = B / G -  D / G -  F * A / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "x = B / G / C -  D / G / C -  F * A / G / C"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_498", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u273e \u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2659"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_498", "raw/question": "- D + A - G / F - C * B * x = 0", "raw/answer": "x = -  D / C / B + A / C / B -  G / F / C / B", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "A - G / F - C * B * x = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- G / F - C * B * x = D - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - G / F to the right side", "equation": "- C * B * x = D - A + G / F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "C * B * x = -  D + A -  G / F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * C to the right side", "equation": "B * x = -  D / C + A / C -  G / F / C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * B to the right side", "equation": "x = -  D / C / B + A / C / B -  G / F / C / B"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_499", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u263a \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_499", "raw/question": "D = B + A * G * x / F + C", "raw/answer": "x = D / A / G * F - B / A / G * F - C / A / G * F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B + A * G * x / F + C = D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "A * G * x / F + C = D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "A * G * x / F = D - B - C"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "G * x/F = D / A - B / A - C / A"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "x/F = D / A / G - B / A / G - C / A / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / F to the right side", "equation": "x = D / A / G * F - B / A / G * F - C / A / G * F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_500", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_500", "raw/question": "- A - D = B - F + C + G - x", "raw/answer": "x = A + D + B -  F + C + G", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "B - F + C + G - x = - A - D"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- F + C + G - x = - A - D - B"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "C + G - x = - A - D - B + F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "G - x = - A - D - B + F - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "- x = - A - D - B + F - C - G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x = A + D + B -  F + C + G"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_501", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u273e \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_501", "raw/question": "- B + G * A * x - C + D - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / G / A + C / G / A - D / G / A + F / G / A", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "G * A * x - C + D - F = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "G * A * x + D - F = B + C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "G * A * x - F = B + C - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "G * A * x = B + C - D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "A * x = B / G + C / G - D / G + F / G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x = B / G / A + C / G / A - D / G / A + F / G / A"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_502", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2730 \u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2740 \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u26ed \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2740 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_502", "raw/question": "- C + A + B + G / x + D - F = 0", "raw/answer": "x = G / (C - A - B - D + F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "A + B + G / x + D - F = C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "B + G / x + D - F = C - A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "G / x + D - F = C - A - B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "G / x - F = C - A - B - D"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "G / x = C - A - B - D + F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "x = G / (C - A - B - D + F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_503", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2659 \u2194 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264b \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u266a \u269b \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u266a \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u264b \u266a \u264f \u273e \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u273e \u269b \u2740 \u26ed \u273e \u269b"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_503", "raw/question": "B = A / C - x / D + F - G", "raw/answer": "x = - B * D + A / C * D + F * D -  G * D", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "A / C - x / D + F - G = B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move A / C to the right side", "equation": "- x / D + F - G = B - A / C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- x / D - G = B - A / C - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - G to the right side", "equation": "- x / D = B - A / C - F + G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x / D = - B + A / C + F -  G"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move / D to the right side", "equation": "x = - B * D + A / C * D + F * D -  G * D"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_504", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2730 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2740 \u264b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_504", "raw/question": "- G = D + B / x * F + A - C", "raw/answer": "x = B / (- G / F - D / F - A / F + C / F)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D + B / x * F + A - C = - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "B / x * F + A - C = - G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "B / x * F - C = - G - D - A"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - C to the right side", "equation": "B / x * F = - G - D - A + C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "B/x = - G / F - D / F - A / F + C / F"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (- G / F - D / F - A / F + C / F)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_505", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2194 \u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u2659"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u269b \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_505", "raw/question": "- C - G = D - B - A * x * F", "raw/answer": "x = C / A / F + G / A / F + D / A / F -  B / A / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "D - B - A * x * F = - C - G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- B - A * x * F = - C - G - D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - B to the right side", "equation": "- A * x * F = - C - G - D + B"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * x * F = C + G + D -  B"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "x * F = C / A + G / A + D / A -  B / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = C / A / F + G / A / F + D / A / F -  B / A / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_506", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed \u266a \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u2740 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u273e \u263a \u2194 \u2659 \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u273e \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u266a \u263a \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u263a \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u263a"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_506", "raw/question": "- x * F + B + G / A - D + C = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / F + G / A / F -  D / F + C / F", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "- x * F + G / A - D + C = - B"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G / A to the right side", "equation": "- x * F - D + C = - B - G / A"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- x * F + C = - B - G / A + D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "- x * F = - B - G / A + D - C"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "x * F = B + G / A -  D + C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move * F to the right side", "equation": "x = B / F + G / A / F -  D / F + C / F"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_507", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u264f \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u263a \u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u263a"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u273e \u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u2730 \u264f \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u269b \u266a \u2772 \u2659 \u266a \u26ed \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u264f \u266a \u264b \u2730 \u263a \u266a \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_507", "raw/question": "- B / G = C + F - A * D / x", "raw/answer": "x = D / (B / G / A + C / A + F / A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "C + F - A * D / x = - B / G"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move C to the right side", "equation": "F - A * D / x = - B / G - C"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move F to the right side", "equation": "- A * D / x = - B / G - C - F"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "A * D / x = B / G + C + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move * A to the right side", "equation": "D/x = B / G / A + C / A + F / A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "x = D / (B / G / A + C / A + F / A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_508", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u264f \u2194 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2773", "num_steps": 7, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if \u2764 is on the right side", "equation": "\u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a to the right side", "equation": "\u264b \u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u264f \u2740 \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2730 \u263a \u2740 \u264b"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u264f \u2730 \u26ed \u2730 \u269b \u2740 \u263a \u2730 \u264b \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_508", "raw/question": "- C = G + D - F + A - B / x", "raw/answer": "x = B / (C + G + D -  F + A)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Swap sides if x is on the right side", "equation": "G + D - F + A - B / x = - C"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move G to the right side", "equation": "D - F + A - B / x = - C - G"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move D to the right side", "equation": "- F + A - B / x = - C - G - D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move - F to the right side", "equation": "A - B / x = - C - G - D + F"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move A to the right side", "equation": "- B / x = - C - G - D + F - A"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / x = C + G + D -  F + A"}, {"step": 7, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (C + G + D -  F + A)"}]}
{"id": "oodtest_509", "variable_num": 7, "question": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u25ef", "answer": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2773", "num_steps": 6, "steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move \u2740 \u269b to the right side", "equation": "\u2740 \u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2730 \u269b"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move \u2740 to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u273e \u26ed \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u2740 \u269b"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move \u273e \u26ed to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u264f \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move \u266a \u264f to the right side", "equation": "\u2659 \u266a \u2764 \u2194 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move \u2659 to the right side", "equation": "\u2764 \u2194 \u2659 \u266a \u2772 \u2740 \u263a \u273e \u264b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2740 \u269b \u266a \u26ed \u273e \u264f \u2773"}], "raw_id": "oodtest_509", "raw/question": "- B / C / x * G - F * A - D = 0", "raw/answer": "x = B / (-  F * A / G * C -  D / G * C)", "raw/steps": [{"step": 1, "desc": "Move - F * A to the right side", "equation": "- B / C / x * G - D = F * A"}, {"step": 2, "desc": "Move - D to the right side", "equation": "- B / C / x * G = F * A + D"}, {"step": 3, "desc": "Move - to the right side", "equation": "B / C / x * G = -  F * A -  D"}, {"step": 4, "desc": "Move * G to the right side", "equation": "B/C/x = -  F * A / G -  D / G"}, {"step": 5, "desc": "Move / C to the right side", "equation": "B/ x = -  F * A / G * C -  D / G * C"}, {"step": 6, "desc": "Move B to the right side", "equation": "x = B / (-  F * A / G * C -  D / G * C)"}]}
